Welcome to the madness
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up a scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Sides twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame this flame the saint your mama
podcast this a runaway train welcome to the madness buckle up tight boot
flashing on cam chat losing their minds Michael getting gong Alex taking flight
it's wild it's wrong and we do it every night he's got him simping hearts in the
chat but she ain't got time for a dude like that diamond flirting hard let the
girls react it's a freak show party no filter all facts yo all facts yo yo
Gone not tonight Alex tried to joke boom sent into the night panel look inside ways
Someone's got a fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirts slipping down low
Oops, she says with a wink. That's the whole show sides half asleep. I still cracking jokes slurred out wisdom with a bourbon so glow
No rules just rolls we pretend to play
And we're trending in the press
Welcome to the madness
Buckle up tight
Boobs flashing on cam chat
Losing their minds
Michael getting gong
To Alex taking flight
It's wild, it's wrong
And we do it every night
Paige got em' simpin' hearts in the chat
But she ain't got time for a dude like that
Diamond flirtin' hard
Let the girls react
It's a freak show
Party no filter
All facts
Yeah
Lights out
The vibe
just right if there's a whole thing for the real and true I'd carve your name in
gold gold
I believe you
Softly where dreams intersect in the twelfth house of fire shadows ignite
Sagittarius aims through the dark toward the light
You love like a pilgrim on paths never known
Seeking the sacred where wild stars are sown
Your heart is a compass it points past the veil
Total of that is bound
This myth on the trail
Hunting for freedom, for truth dressed in black
through the end
Venus and Sagittarius in the 12th house, that's my placement, but it's an interesting placement, if you ever study about the 12th house, it's pretty interesting.
I don't know if I have my camera too close to my face tonight, so I'm right up on my keyboard, I don't know if I need to move it back a little bit, but I do have my
I'm going to put it down a little bit Hi Nancy, how are you?
Okay, let's put it down a little bit and put it up.
There we go.
I think that's okay.
Let's welcome up Juggalette.
what's up how are you doing buddy juggalette you have to be you have to
cam up backstage your baby davis's baby jane photo i just do not trust you i
didn't sleep who this person named juggalette backstage i think i
recognize the name of the porn bomber juggalo yeah don't let anybody name
juggalo up okay juggalette unless you came up within the
next 10 seconds you were not getting on the show
I mean, what's coming up gonna do that stick they can still pull it out. No, I see it. Is it?
No, that ceiling is too clean to be Isaiah
Okay, I'm gonna put on them on the background
They got you juggle it
Jiggle it jiggle it juggle that oh, hey, hello. Hey, when are you gonna dive age?
See oh see
That's not very nice. I knew that was gonna happen. Well, no, whatever. It's fine. I mean, whatever. This is stupid
Yeah, am I gonna die not soon enough for him? He's never gonna die of AIDS. How about that?
I don't have it. Oh, yeah. Yeah, so fuck you asshole. Nobody dies of AIDS anymore dumb dumb. Oh
What is what a dick shit? I mean, it's like
It's going to it's like when people like it's a cam up and then they just came up in there like you know
He was in some kind of dungeon or something. I don't know. I don't understand. It's coming up. What is that supposed to accomplish?
I mean she always are if I know I am now I'm gonna fucking destroy you
I'm gonna drop a bomb on you. It doesn't it means nothing
Yeah, cuz I now I know you are it's a lot different someone drops like a bomb with hiding their hand
You know who they are you know what if they got somebody in the room with them?
They'll just show them and then they'll fucking bomb you and then they'll come back later
I know I mean it's like I mean
Shit who's calling?
It's somebody just playing on my phone. It's just one of my my people my annoying people that harass me
What's on tap?
Yeah, they just can whenever I start to show they start calling and texting and stuff
That's what you should do. You should put up a phone number of people can call in
Yeah, I could I could put up a burner and stuff like that, but I
don't mind people this
Start saying bad things in the thing. Did you see the other night with Chris K. Though Chris K. God
I only saw that thing you posted with the tent
Okay, well, you have to see some of his some of his appearance from the other night. Do you mind how long?
Yeah, go ahead. I wasn't impressed with that 10 shit. So
Well, I think you like this then he dropped the n-bomb on some dude and started fighting them
Are we are we making a celebrity out of it? Yeah, I'm not privately. Okay. Oh, there is I mean
Oh, what are you doing? What's up? What's up? Hey, what's up, bro? What's up? How are you? It looks like I'm good, man
I'm just fucking you know, I got a story
We turn light on here
Listen bro fucking up. I'm getting drunk, dude. Who else is getting drunk one accomplishment?
What's up?
All right, you guys don't even seem what the fucking you know
Another
Are you balls? What's going on? Yeah? Yeah, I must get my skin head. I'm a fucking. I'm a fucking peckerwood, dude
We're talking about fucking I eat all day San Bernardino Peckerwood's
Okay, I dated a pecker wood when I was in LA County jail. I know you told me about it
I know here's me guy. It's like I love you dog. Hey, man. Listen, I'm being serious right now dog
Like fucking I have to move out of here where I live right now fucking. Hey, I might come through
Can I chill? Oh shit?
Yeah
Where you where you're in like Santa Monica or a sense?
On a beach you're on a beach. We got like fucking here's thing bro fucking. Yeah, I'll come to dude type shit
You know me like well
Yeah, you're cool dude like you know fuck. Hey, you think I fucking uh
No, I'm not gonna say down on the internet, you know, okay
What's up privately, okay? He's like
Yeah, it's like I'll let you go like you have an Instagram or something like fucking don't leak your shit. Don't leak your shit, but I
Fuck it. I'll come through it. Listen. I'll have money. I'll have hella money
I have like fucking a hundred thousand dollars doc when I went after I leave this house. I have a hundred thousand dollars
Those beard hairs and glue them to his head. Yeah, we'll fucking a we'll listen
Hey money talks, bro. You guys want to see me in psych fucking on chatter bait?
You should have just stopped it. How much fucking
How much you know what I mean like I'm down. I'm do you know me touch it?
So anyway, nice, okay here. Here's the kitty cat
Yeah, I was like, you know, I mean I was like have my hat. I was on my hat
I'm like, hey, I'm like, hey, it's like, hey, bro, hey, bro.
You know what I mean?
But yeah, he's a fucking, I'm a fuck.
I shave my head all day, like, I'm a fucking Aryan brother.
Do you know what I mean?
So that's it.
He needs to loosen his wrist a little.
I don't want to hear it.
White power, dude.
White power.
Are you really into that?
Or is it like, I don't think it down.
No, I'm fucking.
I'm fucking.
Oh my god.
Dude you white powered your own panel
Not mean to I mean he was talking about like the power of like
Maybe meant the color white. Yeah, I think the color way too. Yeah. Yeah, not the people my gosh
But God this has been exciting. We're gonna do chatter be together. Oh, I can't wait to see this fucking train wreck
You know what? It'd be great. Oh, yeah, I'll be right there fucking front row
Can't I'm excited with your 100 grand. That's gonna be fun. He's gonna stay at your place. Yeah, hopefully my bed
Oh, that's gonna be great. That's yeah, we can't wait to watch this ratings ratings ratings
Guys behind the scenes of the chatter bait thing
Why don't you invite Mason over and fucking have an orgy with the fucking tree?
I know I'm Mason
he sounds like he would too he would and Mason likes me I think Mason's like he's not sure he's not sure but he's ready to try it
he's so innocent he's innocent that's why I feel bad I'm like I think I got you corrupting him yeah
he's like what do you mean I'm fully there I'm like I know you're a nice person
it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it
Yeah
That's me by the way
No, actually no, not african-american, sorry
Hindu Hindu
Yeah, thank you come again
I'm sorry, I was bad. I'm gonna get in big trouble now.
I mean, God laughs though. I think it was worth it, right?
I do love Indians. I do love Indians.
That was good. That was good.
Yeah, I don't feel good. I need the wheelchair today.
God, did you ever see Tusk?
The movie?
Yeah.
No, he turns the guy into a walrus. Yeah. I didn't see it. It's like I got anything in a wheelchair and stuff
It's like an old man, you know, and it's like he leaves like a little like notice in the men's bathroom in some bars
Hey, do you want to come and like here's some some interesting stories from like, you know from an old man
This guy's like, uh, you know the radio show called what's it called? It's called
Yeah, but
Yeah, he has this we're radio show with a dumb name, but anyway, so he goes and he meets this guy and the guy
Talking about old first stories that I won't ruin it, but it needs to be the guy
Well, I'm never gonna watch it. So oh the guy put something in his drink and the guy wakes up
He's like in this checkerboard floor in this big ballroom and the guy comes out and he's like, oh, what happened?
He's always all like waking up. He's like, oh my gosh, and he's like sitting in the chair
You guys oh my god, you got bit by a spider last night. They did he's like yeah in your leg
and the guy like pulls off his
Off his blanket. He has his leg removed. Oh shit
Yeah, see those movies are fucking gruesome, man. I
Watched all three of those. Um, fuck it. What is it those fucking?
Centipede movies human center. Oh, I don't like those. I don't like that with the German
Yeah, what the fuck was I'm like, what am I? I felt so fucking like
Watching shit like that. Well, what are they?
Don't like like a spit I spit in your grave. I don't like that movie. I don't like um, yeah
I don't like shit like that either. It's fucking nasty very like revenge movies, but not like that. Oh, yeah
The revenge movie is like what's the guy with the grouty Roddy Piper where he's like, you know, that one's good
Well, I guess that's wish that death wish was great one two three. Yeah. Oh, yeah, where he goes out and he's like
Yeah, it's very very music. He just blows people every bench
They raped his fucking wife and daughter and then you had to get like too extreme. Hey Katrina
So Katrina my closet is straight man. I don't think so. I really don't but
You know
Guys nowadays are not even
My hair I'm too impressed with the male population right now. So
I like having friends, I like having friends, right?
You didn't ask me that, hold on, what did it say?
Oh, you said, are you comparing Gotti
to an old man in a wheelchair?
Yeah, I was, okay.
And, oh, Radimus said it, I'm sorry, Radimus said it.
Radimus.
Okay, it was used for that.
The Pumpkin Head movie, I remember Pumpkin Head,
I just watched it recently.
Pumpkin Head was good, the first one was good.
Yeah, he was like he was like nerdy kid in the town. I got killed but I don't really got killed but like
Yeah, or I know that was revenge
It was that was revenge because he did something or he thought he did something
I forgot the premise then the witch did some curse and he came back and he killed everybody who fucked over the daughter assumption
I forget. Oh here. Okay, so we have oji Vato. Oh, oh, I'm
You know who? I was a real one. Yeah, he's real
What is that you?
We're up kid kid
Yes, I'm your father. What the fuck you talking about dog. What are you talking about? You just a lot the shit out you
Anyway, yeah, what do you expect? He's about to man
Well, I'll beat the fuck up to your no G bottle. This is how they talk
We talk this way what we walk this way and we beat the shit out of niggas like you
Not too many culture. What do you mean? What culture are you talking about?
Culture, that's how you did who the fuck are you? What's your name? What do you mean? Do the culture that's God
What do you mean? What do you mean? This is OG God your gay or what the gay culture? Oh, that's that's what you want
Got a pussy
Gay, Mexican, oh, jeez. Are you a homo or no dumb enough?
Shut the fuck up, dude. Hey, sorry. What's up, man?
What's going on man
I think they kick off because you're being rude to the host
No, I'm asking you. What's up, and I'm telling God he is the
I'm gay though, and you're offended me several times you're offended by being called gay
I know you can't see my balls
I can't please oh
Maybe tomorrow and God he's already tried to suck my balls
You can have them. Hey, but though you can have a man. Don't come at me
Yeah, we fight over psych. Are you gay or what are you doing? It's all yours. He's all yours, bro
Whoever whoever whoever
Dicks me down the best
Actually, he's a dog. So look at that cycle. He's looking for my face. I
Am I like your big O right there?
the
This fucking guy
You being penetrated by fucking you were penetrated by yourself my piece. What the fuck?
Got your bitch
Oh, you got got me bitch. It's all right. It's all right. It's all right, man. No trip man. I ain't against you
I'm going that got he's that's all that's not it's like he's talking to you
No, hey, it's like don't cry man
But if you want to kick me off you kick me off, but the it's a first
I
Went too long that went way too long you see that coming. Yeah, I wouldn't have to God alone
I don't I don't think it's the who's this guy trying to get between God and I
Who do you think he's the devil? He's two-dimensional. Yeah pretty boring kid pretty boring character
I mean, he's not didn't even sound like a vato. He sounds like
White guy in like New Jersey or something. I'll put on a voice. Yeah
Eugh, eugh, you supposed to duck like this, essay?
Like that, like real like, like you're from like,
SLA, I don't even know what his voice was.
Too many.
The toilet paper podcast, yeah.
The tortured, tortured peehole podcast.
Forget about these fools, man.
I wanna discuss something with you.
Okay, go ahead.
The future of the show.
Yes, what direction are we going? We're going wherever the
Whether the wind takes me, you know, it's like gonna be
You know, I love doing my side. I know I know Bita had a big problem with me doing it
Yeah, you know what businesses of hers. I don't care if she likes it or not. It's not I'm not doing it for her
I'm doing it for you know, basically
I like it, but I think that a lot of people do like it on the show
I think it is creative. It's like people are like, oh my god
It's not great. What am I supposed to hire like a ten-piece band and you know, right?
Like that has to be how ever it's just like as long as it's no
Well, you do what you like and a lot of people like it. That's good
Maybe I'll have people that come in to do maybe that the people that leave that don't like it whether good riddance or whatever like I
Don't understand like why I have to be told how to run my show and I mean I mean she did start
Probably a few months earlier than me and she knows a lot more people right and she's more popular
It's not a popularity contest like she was talking about oh
Well, Emma and Elisa won't have anything to do with them.
First of all, that's not true.
Well, Emma will, but now they're all
plotting on ambushing her on some interview,
and it's like, whatever, it doesn't
sound like friendly to me, which we're going to try to deal with.
And then what else?
And then Elisa never had a problem with me.
Elisa is awesome.
Elisa Tadano?
Yeah.
Don't know he's he actually just went to her chat and was like, okay. Oh, um, thank you wait in her current friends discord
He's like, oh, thank you weakens, and I got him into that discord by the way
You know, the Seiki Awakens, are you going to tell Elisa that you say you're a better
streamer than her and all this crap you talk about her?
And I was like, Elisa, this guy's just like some hate-traveling gypsy, hate-easy, and
Elisa, this guy's just some bitter-beddy that I got out of my chat, or I'm off my
panel for having a shitty microphone, and he's just mad and trolling.
She's like, oh honey, I knew that, like two minutes later, she wrote back, and so I don't
know.
I mean, it's like...
he's not going to pick, I don't know, she's not going to, you know, it's a fish upper and him and crew
right now, right now you've kind of plateaued, you know what I mean, once you stop dwelling on these past events and these past people, you're going to start climbing again
Yeah, I think I'm I think I'm blind. I think I'm doing fine. I've 30 people here now. This is not bad
It's like not like great 30 people's good. Yeah, but get back to basics
Stop doing what you like start doing the tarot readings and you know go from that
I got Tara reading tonight. I got the cats here. I got the panel open and
You know, it's a nice night. Let's go the deck. Let's go man
Reading in fucking like a month. Maybe ready for a reading tonight. Okay, let's do it
What do I do? How many cards do you want tonight?
Let's do five cards.
Okay, five cards? Okay, do you want to tell me how to,
or how many times to cut the deck or something?
The pentagram of cards.
How many what?
Like, you can tell me when to stop and stuff,
while I'm shuffling.
Are you shuffling?
Yeah, yeah, keep shuffling.
Okay, I'm shuffling.
And then just tell me to stop five times, okay?
I'm counting in my head.
Okay.
All right, okay, that's one. Yep. Okay
Okay, go whenever you want
five
Okay
It's the fifth no, this is the third
No, it's the fifth. Oh, there's a bit. Okay. Oh, yeah, so I'm just tell me to stop three more times. I get things over
Stop
Three, okay, two more, okay
Keep going
Right there. Oh got it. Okay one more
Right there, okay, so we got three go
Gotty, okay, first we have okay seven of one this is trapped, but who is the monster?
So the seven of one what deck is this this is called the horror tarot
The horror tarot. Oh look how the green screen goes on that cool
So this is like you know
This is on the defensive, but it's not like you know the nine of ones is more hardware
They're on the fence than the nine of ones get like a bandage around their head. So that is more trauma
This is more of like, you know
You're in your you're not traumatized and you're strong and but you do have like coming up to you for maybe the wrong reason
Say who's the monster here? It's like more like they're the monster. They're saying you're the monster that kind of thing
But it's just as beyond your guard or you've been you've been on your guard. You've been defensive and you've really can't kind of
Bought off some people. Oh, we have another. Oh, we have another seven. Okay, so this is a seven always the monster
So this one says look upon my works and so you've been working on yes, behold
Yes, the whole look upon my works and like, you know, it's actually like even raising the dead. Maybe it takes some kind of
It's something that's kind of me or at least like raising people from their regular consciousness
It's like a higher consciousness. Maybe like, you know and raising the legions
Energy and things around there just like harvesting cards, you know the harvest, okay?
What else we got? Okay, then we got we have the exorcist with a page of one. Oh, nice
The Linda Blair exorcist is gonna be like a younger person that it's gonna
Tell you or give you something that's gonna
Also, we spirit. Yeah, thank you. I think you'll be passionate about whatever this person
Introduces you to you know, I think that I might have a good idea something that's gonna inspire you, okay?
Also, we have you as the king of cups, there you are, there you are, look at that, of course
the king.
Yeah, and this is like, you know, really mastery of your emotions, like, you know, a comp
pool collected, you don't let anybody, you have your skin or bother you, it's just like,
you know, you're in control, very true.
Yeah.
Okay, also maybe like have a drink once in a while, and then we have, we have the aid
of pinnacles, this is called the collector, that's a great card.
Yeah, he's collecting like these different women's heads. You can see the cutting off that one. But yeah
trophies
Yeah, but maybe these are like mines. Maybe these are like, you know, you're using some mines on your side and browns
Yeah, so also, there's the seven of pinnacles. And so this is the eight of pinnacles
This is the progression of that material thing that's going on and I think that the passion is gonna take you higher through
Okay. Yeah, that's great. Yeah, so that's your thank you, bro
No works for me
So you're talking about Alistair Crowley in the chat.
The magic of the science and art of causing change
to her form into will, right?
Do it, that will be the whole of the law.
It's about, you know, basically your will being done,
we have to remember there's a lot of people
that have wills and so if you're not supposed
to really interfere with other people's wills,
you're supposed to let everybody have free will.
And so that's kind of like one of the rules is like,
You have your own free will but don't get in the way of anybody else's
Then that kind of opens up to your self. I've read a lot of Crowley like a lot of Crowley and
And you recognize him as a very trickstery
Guru type of person you need a reason that goes with the whole controlling your panel kind of thing
Yeah, yeah, they wanted to take your free will from you
Yeah, they try to take the free will and that's like that's not right
And so it's like I have to fight back. It's a I have to spend my fuel you get a card yet
Katrina
He like you like the deck sure I got your new card and with and goes if you want to do a reading come on up here
But you just want one card to turn it up. Tell me if you want more about
This one popped out
Okay, you got the nine of pentacles. This is like it's a nine of pentacles. It's in the lap of luxury
Okay, and nine of pentacles is usually this woman walking on this beautiful garden
It's just like there's a lot of bounty a lot of abundance around you also
Getting what you want. You've gotten something you want and materially also having everything you need
There's a big satisfaction here. Just one one one
Technical away from this like this also this like long-term wealth that you're really seeking it
I know you want to pass it down and stuff. Okay, some are some are we like when if you want more cards
Katrina just let me know but I say that's a good part of just like, you know, enjoy what's around you
enjoy the bounce full of fun it's around you and
Thank you. Thank you for your blood.
Okay, I got you. I got you summer. I got you.
Okay, I got you to our bitter all be right there with this. I'm just gonna do summer real quick. Okay three cards for summer. Okay?
Okay summer we got okay
Summer we okay, we're starting out with this king of pentacles. Okay, so this is
This could be your husband or could be yourself, but it's like, you know, this is like having a
Having somebody that you can be abundant with that's cool. Yeah
That's pretty it says says I'm the king of pentacles the man who has everything. So, you know, I think that
But where we're with he's also very satisfied with things. There's also this is a hermit card right now
It's like basically encouraging you to
to withdraw a little bit
You know
Collect your collector thought collect yourself enjoy time alone take a walk alone. Maybe I'm saying like
Take a walk somewhere like I think it's you know nice walk and just like a meditate while you're walking and then I think
like sometime alone and like or sometime at least withdraw from something and then it's like that
will bring you towards this um like romance the two of cuffs and so i think that well you know
my spice things up in the long run okay um yeah can i bought in a mod just hide oji buster he was a
buster right okay so uh yeah oh oji bata okay oji bata was a buster anyway sorry sorry summer so
this is the two of cuffs this means after to be like you know a little bit of withdrawing it's like
back to like some kind of romance and back to the two of Cubs that's basically coming together.
Get together a romantic word of their soulmate and see that kind of coffee there or something,
but um there is having a little dance. Let me see if I have a word of advice for somewhere.
Okay um okay so let's give the word of advice is like a hierarchy. Maybe it's going to be like
renewal of that. Wow it's kind of scary to deliver that. Yeah renewal of vows this could be um or
Or it could be basically being called to the higher cause and I know you feel like you are definitely.
Oh, it's ill.
Yeah.
But the higher fit, right?
It could be either and also like really setting some kind of tradition in a very serious way.
A church or community organization or yeah, that is a skeleton and so and this pope was it says he sees through the material world
And into your very soul. Yeah, that's
So these folks can do but yeah
Maybe you have that you you have that you have that ability too
I think you can like see through the material world and see into souls. Let's see looks like they want to link it
I think
This is where I was looking for something more personal what's going on. It's like, oh, I'm sorry. Oh, I'm sorry
Okay, come on up, I apologize, hold on, I can be preliminary.
It's not, it's just happening not wrong,
but it's like, yeah, we're at some point
to do like a question.
Okay, I didn't say anything wrong with your relationship,
I said.
No, you said he's very satisfied.
Yeah, but it's okay, it's okay,
that's why sometimes it's better to have a conversation.
And so, I apologize, I should have put it up.
more careful about reading okay here we go. Hi. Yo summer. Hey what's up everybody? Hello.
Sorry okay go ahead and ask questions. That's right. Go. How are we doing tonight?
God is that
He doesn't sound like ghost
It sounds like Tony
You did for me, I'm not gonna lie. All right get over it
You know what I'm trigger, and I'm gonna leave it and I'm trigger
Summer's not in the mood for your shit
Okay, so summer did you have a question?
Just more like not relationship shit cuz my relationship
Yeah, okay, but what's your question about? I
Don't know just in general more in general
How many cards would you like? May I suggest the animal card? I know
How many cards did you like summer?
Seven okay, yeah, it's like a 70, okay
I'm going to mute.
Three, four, five, six, OK.
Okay, well you're coming out as the Queen of Wands, okay?
So you're coming out as the Queen of Wands that says courage, confidence, independence, and determination, okay?
So you've got these qualities very strongly
and also, you know, it's very passionate. You've been in control of your passions at the same time, and then we have the Devil card, okay?
This could be...
You know a lot of times it's like, you know, you heard her lower nature, but it could just be very down like down to earth and stuff like that
And not in a negative way necessarily also
You in control of
People that kind of need help that need to that need to have the strings pulled a little bit
You'll just come up with a strength card the strength part says a contest between the most
powerful most terrifying creature alive and a lion
You know, it's like it's like, you know, it's it's had the strength is not enforced
It's it's in the strength of hearts and this and some gentleness and that actually actually
Be a better way of dealing with people. All right, you have some like something really
I think you might have something coming up really fast like some some news that might might
that might
Feel it might be sad. It's like it looks like a shake-up because you got the tower the three of three of swords
Okay, and then the communication that's the day of ones means something coming in with the baths
This one says change is coming something is in the air action
The time is now where will you be with a big event happens and then the tower is kind of sick
I'm gonna big event happening
But
After that I have this seven of swords. Okay seven of swords
Okay, so seven of swords is traditionally I would say like a beef cart
So you might want to just make sure everything is secured, right? All yours of is secured keep your keep your
You know eye on your bank account and all these kind of things
Because you know we wouldn't want that to be
The the shake up the kind of theft or something like that. Let me see I need a clarifier for like the overall
Okay, yeah, there's a lot of possibilities.
It's eight of causes.
It can be a lot of possibilities, a lot of options,
but also you have a lot that's making you happy
and to just be careful about leaving unattended
to go look for something else.
This is like, yeah, I see this as like,
don't leave something unattended
because there's a thief around, okay?
Just beware, because I think you can stop it.
I think that could be a warning to prevent it, so.
That made more sense for you. So, oh
Yeah, there's a thief of life that's going on right now, okay
Yeah, that's more accurate than
Okay
Run that shit the proof of burden is on you. Hey, what's up?
It's still my goddamn reading
The double-card I see like there could be like
Somebody like around like around you is like yeah, it's like a spiritual that's kind of like that kind of like a light
We've got a little light or light
What kind of feet did you say I
Lost three people this week, so I would say a thief of life. I got you
Yeah
Yeah, well when I know what I just got I just got the seven of pentacles. Okay, so this is it
There will be a, there will be a, God got this card because this is like, you are able to like really inspire people and bring people to life and think, okay, that'll be okay, that'll be okay.
So I would say like this is, probably the advice is to just continue, continue to do that and also, this is a harvest card too, and so you're gonna be collected, like make sure you get to collect.
You're trying to collect and
I'll be right back okay
Hello, hello. Oh, I just missed Goddy. What's the fuck?
Did I scare him off?
No, you didn't
All right, well, thank you psyche. You're welcome. I hope you liked it summer. I hope it's helpful
I did. Thank you. You're that you're that you're that queen energy. Don't forget and so, you know, it's like you're able to
Fire through all this stuff. So I
Love you
Okay
Hey everybody off goddamn LD. Let's have a debate. How many bitches did you bang in here the proof of burns on you?
in here
I thought you got all the bitches, bro. I'm in my house. I'm a dude. Oh, where do you sleep with people?
You don't scare nobody off so I don't know the fuck you keep saying that you're just a fucking weirdo
Okay, I know people that you have physically fucking done shit to that somebody in my chat
That's why the other day when you up there you hurt somebody's girlfriend. That was in my chat
So you don't care a goddamn thing off. You're a strong ass weird-looking motherfucker
So to ever think you could scare anybody off you fucking bitch boy understand
So stop fucking saying that I left because my reading was over. So don't say you scared anybody
Cuz you ain't shit to be scared of
Baby go take a
So just make sure I clarify that because every fucking time you come up and I leave you're always like, oh
Would I scare everybody off? You'd have to be happy to have a fucking man to scare somebody off. You're a fucking boy
You're a fucking weirdo
Alright, go back to the trailer. I love sitting and telling weirdos. They ain't shit. Yeah. Yeah, hold on, baby
Ghosts I'm only your ghost. I'm here to warn you dickhead
You sound exactly like random guy your voice box is fucking up buddy. No, this is Tony
I know dickhead Tony Randall
It is Randall ghost. You're all the same. I've been my theater for a long time
But now you're not being ghost. You're being random with gold shit
This is my cat Lola
You know stay and fix the voice thing. I don't know what you guys do with these voice things
Have become like 10 different people
Yeah, like I'm random. I'm Tony. I'm ghost like I'm this you're all the same piece of shits, but you know once in a while
I
True voice nice Tony be the by the way. That's not a real voice
Welcome to reality everybody. There's nothing. I'm huge and you're so cute
No
Okay, I thought so
No, no, yeah, but you you sit on this little fucking hill like everybody's fucking scared of you anybody's scared of you
You're just a fucking weirdo dude, so I
Don't know the fuck you get that everybody's scared of you shit
Everybody fucking scared of you. Have you seen yourself?
It was a joke
It's a little fucking irritating. It's like you say it every single time. Oh go change your fucking
Like joking what fucking weird motherfucking like you
it's a
You know her brain just works in
She's awesome follow her lead bro stick with her. That's a good friend
Thanks
You guys I'll see you guys were beat us today like she was kind of like you know
She's kind of very mad at me of course, but oh, I'm sorry old D. You're not chop liver by the way
I heard it the other night. I go to my chop liver
I love you too, bro. I was just
Yeah, you would like a fucking brother waiting valid. I'll talk to y'all later. Yeah, whatever bitch. All right. Yeah. All right back to West Virginia
What'd you do this time melody
Some bitch on the fucking rag I guess
No, no, no, like what was she thought like on the stream you like hooked on
I don't know who the fuck he is
Smacked around a little bit like what'd you do?
I don't know who the fuck that bitch even is. So, that's crazy. I'll be back too guys. See you soon
Where you been?
Where you been the Queen?
Rando, how are you tonight? Oh, dude? I don't know. I'm tired. I'm gonna sleep soon. All right
Okay
Yeah
So, uh, yeah
You guys take it easy
So, uh, so LD do you see what Chris K said the other night?
No, I've been busy at work man. Oh, you didn't okay. Let me show you really good. So what do you say?
Summer's back
Some bitch on the rag. Hey LD. You know a guy named Chrissy Wolf and his girlfriend. You know her you remember her
Crazy you mean the guy that used to suck steaming ass candy stick
You mean you
What girl
His his bitch that you took advantage of and got her all fucked up remember that who's his bitch remember that
So don't tell me I'm some bitch on the rag. I just don't have no problem sitting here fucking talking about predators like you remind me
Who's his bitch?
Shit, you knew the guy I was talking about so you know the bitch I'm talking about
He mask he was blowing ski mask the whole fucking time suck in his dick
Oh, yeah, no, his bitch you were fucking with and you fucking
Broke and took advantage of all this other crazy shit you fucking weirdo
What are you talking about?
I don't have to blast the victim's name all over the fucking place
But you know who the fuck I'm talking about because you knew the guy was talking about so don't be a little bitch
And I'm not a bitch on a rag. I don't have no problem telling a fucking predator. He ain't shit
Coming from the bitch. It's got a hider fucking face
Bitch, I don't ever have my face. I'm always on this motherfucker. I am always
Shit around here, bitch
That's why everybody and their mother jumped up around in that that's why you're not even allowed in half the fucking places
You don't have fucking stupid
Motherfuckers don't fuck with you because you're a fucking predator fuck you I do what I want
I know you do you take advantage of all kinds of bitches, don't you all right now go outside the trailer
Go get your fucking welfare check out of the PO box and shut the fucking welfare check
I'll run circles around your little sorry ass
I'm sure you will cuz you don't have a fucking car
Yeah, I don't have a car. I don't have a car bitch. Please you live in your mother's basement bitch. Why on everything I got bitch
I got a whole house bitch. Yeah, I'm sure you do
Live with your mom. You want to you want to turn your camera on? I'll go. I'll go say the whole fucking house
But so you shit you're a fucking predator dude. You don't run a goddamn thing
You don't run shit
Okay, everything everything. Okay guys. I was gonna I was gonna show this clip of Chris K. Do you see it summer?
You can show the clip
I just wanted to make sure that he know he ain't a bit of bitch and ain't nobody right bitch on a period
I'll be I don't give a fuck where I'm at how I am at wherever you are
I have no problem telling you you a shit you're a fucking predator you take advantage of fucking women
You nasty motherfucker like oh like oh
Like I don't need to put victims out, but you know
You know what the fuck I'm talking about bitch
No, I don't you did
Because you mentioned a guy's name I'm supposed to know his current girlfriend
It ain't his curl girlfriend. It was a it was somebody this happened. I'm a couple you like what two years ago three years ago
How many bitches if you took a van
Was his girlfriend is that who you're talking about now? No, I'm not talking about Gucci
Well, I don't know who the fuck you're talking about this. Yeah, I bet you're not. But what did you take advantage of that part two?
She came to my fucking apartment in Vegas and we fucked
Well, that's not what I'm talking about you dumb fuck. No, I can't remember every fucking slag I hit
Yeah, every slag you take advantage of right
Yeah
Sorry my memory ain't that fucking good
Like I said, you're a fucking predator. So any here and you're the bitch hiding your fucking face
Bitch, you think you can manipulate me to show you face my face. I'm on this bitch all the time. So my goddamn face
Let's suck a dick. Oh
Some of us are busy with jobs. They can't we can't be here every fucking second
What business do you own bitch what business do you own please tell us
None, I'm a W2 employee
Yeah, well, I go work for somebody else
Yes, I'm a payroll employee
Kids I didn't I didn't know fucking hookers file a 1099
Bitch, I own businesses. I don't fuck you. I don't know what you're talking about. I own businesses
You can get all your tips back now. It's never you couldn't yours on your best fucking day. You could never motherfucker
What couldn't what?
Ever stand even close to any my shit is better than you motherfucker. I understand that
Uh, yeah, well whatever bitch. I think I'm gonna you think I gotta prove myself to a predator
You think I gotta prove myself to a predator bitch. You're after goddamn mine. All right. Well
What's that make you an alien?
Yeah
Like I said, you're a bitch whatever I
Don't care I know you don't cuz everybody tells you
Don't care what they fucking tell me come up here and show me
Show you shit bitch. Everyone's got a big fucking mouth. So you get punched in the fucking jaw
Why you're
Bitch you're so goddamn strong and you don't even are you fucking kidding me my fucking shit tards bigger than yellow bitch ass
Probably a what do you like 300 pounds turn that camera on let's see. Yeah, I'm 300 pounds
You don't manipulate shit motherfucker. All right
And I'm gonna sit on your scrawny little bitty ass bitch
Go eat your TV dinner and shut the fuck up. No, I need more than TV dinner
But I need like two roasts and everything. I don't shut sit up. Shut me up, bitch
You'll get some beef ramen. We're gonna shut me up. It's shut me up
Shut yeah broke-ass bitch. You wish broke me. Shut me up, bitch
I'll walk you around the house. Come on
Suck my dick! I gotta show you shit, bitch!
Who the fuck you think I am?
You think I'm one of these low-calculated
internet that you all motherfuckers talk?
Show me your house! Show me your back!
Bitch, suck my dick!
Cause you're fucking fake, bitch.
Yeah, I'm fake. I sure as fuck am.
Yeah.
That's exactly what I want you to think, bitch.
I'm sure.
Yep.
I don't even know who the fuck you was.
Well, you don't need to know who the fuck I am, bitch.
Yeah, I know who you are good. I'm glad
You like that a packer would and then he was like troll P you
What listen bro fucking I'm getting drunk dude who else is getting drunk
What's up
All right, you guys don't even seem with the fucking you know
What are you talking about
Are you bald? What's going on? Did you have hair fuck? Yeah? I must get my skinhead. I'm a fucking. I'm a fucking peckerwood, dude
What are you talking about fucking ie dog all day? San Bernardino peckerwoods?
Okay, I
Dated a peckerwood when I was in LA County Jail. I know you told me about it. I know. Hey, here's the guy
It's like I love you dog
Hey man, listen, I'm being serious right now dog like fucking I have to move out of here
Where I live right now fucking hey, I might come through. Can I chill?
Yeah
Where you were you in like Santa Monica or a sentence?
On a beach you're on a beach. We don't like fucking here's thing bro fucking. Yeah, I'll come to dude. You know I mean like fucking
Yeah, you're cool, dude, like you know, fuck. Hey, you think I fucking
No, I'm not gonna say it online on the internet, you know, okay, okay, we'll hug privately. Okay. Oh, yeah
Yeah, but like you think like
Yeah, it's like I'll hit you up like you have an Instagram or something like fucking don't leak your shit
Don't leak your shit, but I'm all
I'll fucking I'll come through you listen. I'll have money. I'll have hella money
I have like fucking a hundred thousand dollars doc when I would have to leave this house
I have a hundred thousand dollars in my bank
Yeah, we'll fucking a world listen a money talks broke you guys want to see me and psych fucking on chatter bait
How much how much how much you know what I mean like fuck I'm down. I'm do you know I mean type shit
So anyway, nice. Okay here. Here's the kitty cat
Yeah, I was like, you know, I mean I always like have my hat. I was on my hat
I'm like hey, I'm like hey psych. Hey, bro. Hey, bro. You know me. Yeah, they fucking am I fuck
I say my head all day locked. I'm up. I'm a fucking uh airing brother, dude
Okay, so you're gonna let you're gonna let somebody like that come to your house like or is that a joke, right?
Well the other 100 grand and he's all the more rooms
You're your brother
Oh my god, well, you know, I don't know how serious he is about that. I mean, I think that's pretty
Yeah, I mean, I mean he's got some issues. We've all heard some of this shit
He said I mean look what he's done to a homeless person if you're gonna do something like that to a homeless person
You really ain't should you know that right?
Yeah, I mean that was bad. I mean that was terrible, but I mean I believe in like also like, you know
there's karma and stuff like that because
If you ever saw this short clip, this was a this was Chris K at uh, you know, there's this interesting person you got into a fight with
And this is like a little relief, okay, so here we go you guys will like this one
Fucking bitch boy, you just you really do like a fuck of weirdo. It's hilarious actually
This is good
We unexpected I was at dinner with my daughter sitting next to a neurologist one of those highly paid guys who stuck
What the hell is that bike
You know what I mean, so that's it.
Bounce, chicka-bounce.
Well, bitches.
Caller.
There we go.
Yeah, I got it.
This is funny.
Don't get the stupid fucking fool, Potter.
You better check yourself.
What are you doing, buddy?
I ain't no pussy.
Now, get on camera.
Do all that.
I ain't no punk.
You better check yourself.
I don't give a fuck.
Where you going?
Check yourself, Potter.
What the fuck?
Hey.
It would have been a great if I came up and busted him right in his shit that day.
Well, but they're just off a teepee.
That should have been fucking faggot.
We're talking about winner out one.
Yeah, what's up?
What's up?
Fucking bigger.
What's that?
Fucking pussy.
Well, let me watch you talk.
What's up?
What's up, man?
Big motherfuckers like him can hit him in that jaw, and they'll knock right the fuck
on the ground.
Pussy.
Right the fuck out, bro.
When ticket
Well, he was in my city somebody to see no fucking what a homeless person later got out of the car and knocked him the fuck out
Baby, put that big motherfucker down
I'm not playing with you. I'm not now what?
Bruno Mars. Yeah, so yeah, yeah, come to the face by the
Yeah, yeah, I remember some of the same that
I hung out with Chris K a couple times I was living in Vegas. Oh
Was that?
Yeah, we had a good time me him wappy flanker
You know we go out and stream together
Why doesn't that fucking surprise me a fucking
Impestible idiot like that and a fucking weirdo like you hanging out. I bet that was fucking
Just the locale of them all
You know, it was funny as you came in my chat the other day, right?
Cat got he of them was up on panel got he sent the link you came in my chat
And you know what I'm talking about because the person was talking to you why you were in chat
That's what's so funny why you're sitting here acting like I don't know what the fuck I'm talking about
You're talking about crazy. Yeah, I'm talking to you. Yeah, I'm talking about crazy
You know exactly who the fuck and what I talk about do with his girlfriend again. I don't know who the fuck his girlfriend is
Of course you don't of course you don't
Why would I know who your friend is?
Yeah, well, I guess you just take advantage of so many bitches. That's you know your thing
I guess so you probably would forget that predators probably can't keep up with their victims, right?
But like I said, I'm not sitting here just talking out of my ass because you know exactly what the fuck I'm talking about
I don't even I don't know
A lot of people said a lot of shit about you and I was like, oh no, but you know what?
He's got just too much weird shit around him
I'll just stay cool with it
But then he came in the chat and I see him with you and what Chrissy was sitting there fucking saying and it validated any and everything
I needed to know about your sorry ass
So don't think anybody's ever running from a bitch boy like you
Yeah
Because this is one female that would never run from a fucking weirdo like you
I can promise you that I
Have no problem telling anybody that I think it's a piece of shit there a piece of shit
Wow, you're just a strong individual. I
Know ain't I
You're an inspiration my 500 pounds me and my 500 pounds
When you got 500 pounds on you yeah, you can get a little strong
I said 300
Well, I'm you know added 500 you said that
You know
And I'm not the only one that says these if I can wear it out, so there's that too
Yeah
There's a lot there's so much said online that it's like I mean well, yeah, but I know somebody personally that they're they're
Person was involved with him situation. So I don't have to listen to everything else is on
I haven't said anything to him up until then until he came in my chat
And I'm crazy we're talking about what fucking happened not even now
You're like I talked to somebody who also talks to somebody who had something like wow it's fourth degree bullshit
Talking about it in my fucking chat you jackass that doesn't make it real
Really because the conversation you two were having sounded fucking damn. Well, we're old of me
You sure you knew what the fuck was I was being talked about when you were my fucking chat weren't you wouldn't even talk it to him
Didn't you I don't think I really saw it fucking stupid. Don't act fucking dumb
You're supposed to be there's a big bad LD. Why don't you fucking stand on what you saying do bitch?
You're gonna have to remind me what I said, and I didn't need to remind you because you know exactly what the fuck I'm talking about
No, I don't read minds
Yes, I just told you and you've been fucking sitting here answering me when I was sitting there talking about it
So I act like you don't know what I'm fucking talking about you dumbass
All I said was I know Chrissy and I know used to suck ski mask Andy's dick. That's all I said
We're talking in my chat about the situation
All right, again, you're gonna have to remind me about what situation I don't need to remind for shit
Alright, well, I don't read minds I just know now I don't have to listen to things that I didn't know about but now I know for sure
Wow
You're a fucking weirdo thing. Oh, so everybody's gonna run for me for what?
Who the fuck you think you are you ain't nothing you just take advantage of people that you think you can take advantage of you
Can't take advantage of nobody that I'll ever deal with your sorry ass
The ski mask Andy bisexual
If you donate enough probably
Crazy crazy used to make rap songs about ski mask Andy. They were like love ballads. I
Just remember saying to prank call. It's like
I spoke blunts on my stream. Yeah
I know he's playing dumb Samantha, but like I said he knows and I know what the fuck he's talking about because this should just happen the other fucking night
Again you have to remind me I'm probably drinking mind you a shit bitch
But then I don't recall of course you wouldn't recall that's what predators say
You have a lot of it you have a lot of experience for predators
You seem like you're talking from experience you seem to know so much about yeah
I put them I put them in prison actually if you'd like to know that oh, yeah
As of right now, I've got two sitting on trap trial that are about to go to prison. Well, then they're not in prison you dumb bitch
They're on trial
We've already put we've already put at least ten we've already put ten in prison and now
Wow, thank you very fucking much bitch. I ain't gonna lie about the work I do
Yeah, I'm sure
All predators should be off the fucking streets
Yeah
That why you got to hide your face because you're just deep undercover. No, I don't have my face
Like how many times have my face been on this goddamn thing?
I don't have a shit channel. She does a she's a outreach. I go my mouth
He knows he was just trying to pop up on my channel the other night
He did it twice because Goddy Simpson link
Yeah, and then him and Chrissy were in the chat talking
About shit he did to a female
In a bragging way or like a
In a bad way, I've done a lot very bad way. I've done a lot of shit in a very bad way
But you have to remind me I don't know
Specific psyche how many times they say you've been on this panel and I've been over here
I've never said one fucking thing because tons of people say all kinds shit
But now that I know because he came to my panel and talked to somebody in my panel that I know
And they were talking about the situation.
So he can go fucking suck a dick.
Fuck him.
Is that the proof that you bring to these 10 people
you have in prison now as you just go to the jail
and go, yeah, I talked to somebody in a cell room?
No, there's evidence.
And that's why they go to jail
because they're fucking pedophiles.
Great.
Yep.
Do you have a problem with pedophiles going to jail?
No, I think pedophiles should be killed.
Oh, okay.
Well, me too, but unfortunately
We're not killing them, but I mean well I would kill them
But unfortunately I would go to jail. So and I can't do that, but there's that so the best next thing is put their ass in fucking prison
In general population where everybody can have their filled days with them
Yeah, but just like scheme Afghan either gonna go to protective custody
Well in protecting capacity people get touched all the time
I don't know what you have how many times you've been to prison or not, but protective custody ain't shit
What did I miss I miss anything good?
Just this bitch on the reg screaming. What do you mean? Just this
The one she sounds like a sounds like a forensic was reborn she's like oh my dude
of the
of of of of of of
I didn't do shit a motorcycle fell on her and factor in I was joking about putting her head through the wall
You did it. No, no, dude
She was she was fucking cleaning up and her dad's Indian fell over on her and the fucking the the metal thing on the seat
I forget what it's called. It's like the subframe
I don't know but it's like the the backrest for the seat it came down and just cracked her in the fucking head
She had the four staples
Yeah, so
Well, anyway, your other girls come in anyway, so you have to fucking that's good. I know I'm very excited. Yeah
Hey
Somebody wanted me to give you a message
Oh main
No, you'll see in about two seconds
She said she doesn't want to talk to you anymore
She's into scat now
She does facials with scat
Yeah, it's true
This is the proof your friend of yours body. No, it's a friend of yours actually
Yes, exactly that's you me yep, she said
She's not coming back until you apologize to her
Me or LV both these
I'm not apologizing to nobody.
Well, then she's not coming back, then.
OK.
Thank God.
Oh, shit. Let me change the
That's not
Exactly exactly
It's exactly what she did. That's like everything anybody that's on my mask. What a bitch
Dude, whatever you ever see the Muslim woman put on a mud mask
Muskin net don't look like that. There's like the black or don't look like a black face. I
Do the black charcoal ones too, and you can still tell their face mask
Think I'm getting sick
Fucking neck is killing me
How's everyone doing out there in chat, let's see we have
I'm here. I'd appreciate some prayers everybody
Send in new prayers. Thank you. Thank you, everyone
How these a piece of shit in a fucking weirdo
I'm a I'm an 8000 pray. He knows I don't give a fuck what you are
Well, apparently you you care about me being a weirdo
So that's a lot. You know predators are predators. You know, it is what it is
What's that say on your what's that tattoo Brooklyn, yeah Brooklyn
Brooklyn
Well, I got quiet since I left huh
Let me not interrupt go ahead go ahead
You know what those pieces
I'm 300 pounds got him again
So you know he said I was 300 pounds. Well, he's fucking glasses then take off those sunglasses
Fucking idiot. Well, he's used to dating that girl. She only weighs like 98 pounds
LD how do you do this to people man, how do you turn people off so quickly?
He's fucking disgusting
all the shit I do with people
he looks like shit
he's a strawny ass little fucking bird bird bird
chested looking ass motherfucker
he has no kind of fucking personality
he's just a fucking
you can just tell he's a fucking weirdo
he's getting off on this
I'm sure he is
I see him with a little leather bikini top
he's wearing the other fucking egg
he likes to get beat
sorry bitch
you saw me when I was 15 minutes
That was nice. That was a good book
Yeah, you definitely look like somebody's bitch, that's for sure
Yeah, especially with the collar on
Yeah, hopefully she beat the fuck out of you
No, no, no, yeah down to the ATM
She's paying your bills good for you. No, he's paying the fucking bills. What are you talking about?
He's got trick written all over it
She does but she got an inheritance recently. Yeah, she just
He went to the ATM because he had to get money out
I'll do you paying her?
Yeah, that should cost extra
Told you I know a trick what I see what you get something better than that
Well, like summer
I'm 300 rounds. Yeah, well, it's like tuna you got to pay for a pound. Oh
You know
You could pay me if you ever I would never take anything. You're right. I couldn't afford it. I couldn't afford
Won't you go put a collar until that bitch go walk you again?
Cuz I'm at home drinking and how I drive to her car that would be committing a crime
Of course you are. Oh, yeah, I'm sure you've never committed a crime before
I've never been to jail
Get in bitches drunk and take advantage of them and all this other weird shit. That's not a crime at all
No, I was drunk and they took advantage of me
No, yeah, I'm sure birds have said fucking. Come on, dude. Really you fucking father shit you out. Yeah by fucking Shannon gotty
That's right. That's right. See I'm the fucking victim here. I blocked that out of my mind. I forgot about that
She fucking she took advantage of me while I was drunk
Jesus yeah, and she was stone cold sober. Yeah, I forgot so many horrors from this fucking place over the years
Yeah, I try to I try to block it out. So a lot of them with you involved by the way
Creeps you have to go after all these fucking ugliest man
Forensic was one of the fucking oh Jesus. Yeah, but I never met up with friends like Jesus
Let me let me ask how the fuck
Did her fucking nudes
Get in front of my fucking eyes. How the fuck did that even happen, dude?
I don't know because you didn't give it to me. You didn't fucking give it to me. They went all over the fucking place
I have no I was fucking gore bomb with that fucking image of that fat fucking cunt
Oh well, she's dead now, so let's not talk ill about the dead.
Well, still the fucking horror remains in my mind.
I guess, I guess you could say,
I guess you could say, Goddy, that she turned into a forensic file.
The question is...
I just got that the question is why did you stay on the fucking line with her as she's showing you all that shit?
Guess he likes but he likes that
Didn't love it. He loved it. It's hard to turn. It's hard to turn my camera off while I'm throwing up repeated
Yeah, okay. All right throwing up. Yeah. Yeah, all right. Okay, whatever the same read the same way you got Justine shit
No, justine paid me
And Canadian
Well, I had to you know, convert it to dollars
Yeah, she wasn't paying me in gold bullion
You're disgusting
I'm gonna I'm a capitalist, honey. I
Don't give a fuck what you are. You're disgusting. All right. Well, you're fucking welfare. I'm not talking about sex work
I'm not talking about sex work. I'm talking about you dumb fuck. You're disgusting. All right. Well, that's great
But that's not what the rest of us talking about
I don't give a fuck what anybody's talking about. How about that?
Probably why you're so alone
Yeah, I'm alone. I sure the fuck I'm I'm so alone and now I have no friends no family and I'm a 300 pound bitch
Yeah, why don't you bring your boyfriend on welfare?
You want to bring your boyfriend? I don't have a boyfriend or a husband. I'm just a lonely cat bitch
Holy shit, is this the first time you two met? I got 30 cats
No kids. Oh, okay. That's all I get now. All right. This is the first time I mean cuz who would want to stick that like really see
Nobody cuz I'm a 300 round bitch. She's a fucking whale. Yeah, I
Know you're just making up shit. I never said you have 30 cats
Now I'm telling you I have no I have no husband. I have no kids no boyfriend
I'm a 300 round bitch. It's it's in a fucking track house 24 seven what my 30 fucking get that's what he loves
Oh
It's nothing good on
What do you mean this is great
Hey, sir, can you put a movie on the green screen?
Movie does it work like that or no photos on it or just still photos
It's still photos right now. I think maybe I'm let me check if I can
what a giant picture of yourself up there real quick I want to see how funny
that looks yeah yeah have yourself looking down on yourself how do you
should get a green screen too I have to go on my computer to do that you can
surround yourself with fatties I could do a I could do like a virtual green
That's too artsy
Yeah, I get you use more something more realistic
Like just trying to bring cat bitches over you let me do that next time do that too
Psycho yeah, you something more realistic that makes you look
You look like you went to your an apostle
Turn the water into wine or some shit
No, not like Jesus
God are you ever gonna get me that treadmill so I can get all this fat and that's
Together, no, I'm gonna get you the osempic
Why would you get to it? Why would he buy you a treadmill? He's in a wheelchair
She could push me around. Yeah, that's even better
Yeah, so I can push him on the treadmill, duh, that'd be great. You look like Jerry O'Connell
Is it what is that a mugshot
That makes sure it looks like you're hiding out in the caves of fucking Torah Bora like with the Taliban you have like
Do you have something on the wall psyche?
Yeah, green screen
Oh, okay. Oh
He thinks he's kind of okay. I don't think I am
I don't know. I don't know. I watched that movie today, actually
I did that's the one I watched that's the best one you saw the first one
Yeah, but I heard I heard that there's a new one, but it's a it's got a female in it
Yeah, it's like I think it's a TV show
Is it Jane Wick? Oh is it?
Jane Wick. Yeah, something like that. I haven't seen it, but I just heard about it
I mean it gets kind of weird after the third one
Yeah, I watched the first one today though. I hadn't seen it in a while so that one was hype that was good from beginning to end
Yeah, I like it
They killed my dog
Man when he did that I was like you mother fucker. I was like
And everybody was just like
Do you fuck the round and you're gonna find out buddy?
Hey, I'm gonna kill the animals
You don't kill the animals. It was a cute little puppy plus that was like his wife sent that to him, you know like
I would like to be able to
Nothing puts me in a good mood like people dying
Yeah on TV
I like spy movies and I'm like
Yeah, I love those. You know, you got to watch you got to watch that movie Mandy
That's a great fucking Mandy a great fucking revenge movie
Nick cage you'll love it
Yeah, I like it's fucking it's like kind of like
Like a metaphysical revenge movie real fucking like it gets deep into your head
You know not even watch today, which is like such an old movie
But it was just like you know how sometimes like you're on YouTube like those play the movies or whatever
And so I caught the end of our robot met the one what will Smith?
I was like what the fuck that dude
I saw that when it came out. I don't remember loving it, but I think it was pretty good
Yeah, it wasn't a bad movie actually like it really wasn't it was like it was pretty good
I mean it wasn't like you know the best
But it definitely made you because back then when they made it and now you think about it now
And we're starting to see these robots and we're seeing all this
You know I mean the cars and different things like that that everything's just so
Robotic to be so all the AI. Yeah, it's all gonna. Yeah
Yeah
Yep, so it's like, you know, I know I seen it like when it first came out, but like, you know, again
I was like it made me just think of like like you said that I asked us the car and all this
So I was like I saw a clip of somebody played a clip of a terminator
And I guess it was that clip where they show the robots all like the terminator robots all doing the war in
2029 and I'm like fuck. We're like wait four years away from that shit. It totally happened
Right. Yeah, I mean all they gotta do is produce what they have now and upgrade it and put guns in their fucking hands and boom
We're all dead
Well, that's like everybody always talks about, you know, and I know you hear it to be like, well, we're gonna have a civil war
First of all, I mean, you both know these motherfuckers
I mean, yeah, they might dress up in their camouflage or walk around like they're cool
I'm gonna do something when it comes down to it though
They ain't gonna do a goddamn thing our civil war is gonna be they're not gonna shit
But there's our real civil war are gonna be electronics
Yeah, I could see that
But that's how I believe that that's how they let like bank account
I mean and you see it already test runs happening because remember like when all the plants went down was like in North Carolina
a couple years ago and just all kinds of different things like government buildings are getting hacked
Shit they fucking put out all the judges shit like they put all kinds of shit out
You know what I mean and people just do so you already have people that can hack like that like for real for real
And I think that's how the next
The next year dates gonna happen as all those real hackers they can do anything they could shut down the fucking grid
They could fucking do take over your fucking bank accounts everything like you said they could empty everything out
Yeah, I mean think about cuz like even my house right cuz I have like, you know
My place is only Europe like everything in it all the way from my washer and dryer
Everything is ran off. I can have everything my whole house runs on the app. You know what I mean like
Yeah, well, I don't do it. I won't do it. I
Didn't do it, but you know that that husband I don't have because I'm alone with 300 pound bits
He did he did all that, you know, but whatever
But it's just it's just like, you know, and then all the electronic cars and just ever it just everything is computerized
You know, you know, that shit down with one button. They could just shut down every one fucking button. Yep
Yeah, we see that movie that was on Netflix like two years ago. I forgot the name of it the end of tomorrow
I'm like the exact exactly what they can do
My son and daughter-in-law have one and they I mean they love it like they love it
But I'm just like and I'm like don't get me wrong
I think they're cool cars the concept of it and everything. It's just I'm just like I don't know man
I think they're ugly as fuck and there's no reason for that kind of ugly shit
And they should be cheaper than they are if they're gonna be like if they want people to have electronic cars
But these cars like 80 grand
Yeah, they're too expensive I agree and then if something goes wrong with them like it to cause a fucking arm and a leg to get them
Fixed those batteries batteries the toxic is fuck those batteries. You burn the battery. You can't put it out with water
You gotta use sand or some shit to put out and it's toxic gas that just blows into the fucking sky
It's bad. Well, remember that that Tesla truck or whatever that dude or whatever all that shit was and he went into the front of the
Trump Tires and it blew up or whatever. Yep. Yep
But it didn't blow up because I guess it's all fireproof and shit
So all the inside of it just but but they couldn't put it out with regular shit because of all the different chemicals or shit
Yeah
Yeah, I'm not for all this
No, go ahead. What were you gonna say? I was gonna say I'm not for this green energy the way they do it
But I totally believe in like a solar like if we did solar the right way
Yeah, why not put a panel on every fucking car and let that power the air conditioning or in the radio at least you know
But you still
Until we can do it properly
It makes sense if it works it works, but if they're not gonna do it the right way, what's the point?
Right, I think I think even though everybody's like all the green or whatever it is
You know, I mean the big thing they're all talking about and they try to sell it to you all like it's super healthy
But I don't I mean some of that shit causes more damage than some of the shit we got now
Yeah, no, it's all to make money. It's like they're trying to shift the money from the oil to the fucking green bullshit for themselves
They don't give a fuck about the people. I don't think any of the any of the stuff that they've done
Has made my fucking energy
Bill go down in any way the fucking way anything
Yeah, they have
Because they need the fucking energy for that AI shit and that's gonna fucking cost a lot of fucking power
To get that shit running
Just to run that AI and they need a shitload of that
They don't have the fucking capacity because they got rid of all the nuclear plants
That's the only thing that could run that shit
The nuclear plants can run that and they could run all the fucking cars that if we put them on
Electric vehicles and put power stations everywhere. You could have all the fucking power you want
Nuclear power is the only way to go
Yeah, fucking oil we got enough oil for a thousand years apparently so we can go either way
Yeah, yeah, we do have a lot of oil they product like we have a lot of natural oil right here
Yeah, in our own country, that's what I'm saying like we always talking about worrying about this place over there
And this place over there and we got to be we got to kiss their ass
So we get oil and so like that but it's like dude. We got to hear like the fuck well those bush
Here
Yeah, well, yeah, that's exactly it because they make money off of it. Yeah, he was making money with his boys. Fucker. Yeah, oh fucker family, man
That's a bad that's a bad sign psyche left
He's gonna shut this shit down
That's all right. I'll give you guys an idiot. Sorry. I just don't fucking like him. No, if you don't like him
You don't like him. We could take it
He started all before
I'm sure oh
Fuck I just woke up. I fell asleep for a little for like a while. Oh you slept good then. Oh
Yeah
Yeah, it's not crazy week
I'm surprised you woke up. You should just sleep for another eight hours man. The way it's been going this week. I
Am I'm just I woke up for a minute. I was I got something to eat because I was like that
I didn't even come home and it like why eight when I bought or whatever, but then I fell asleep and then I'm like I woke up
I'm like back. I'm hungry
So I ate something and jumped on here for a second and
probably go away back to you
Hmm fuck
Fun fun fun
How was your week? I had a good week. I can't complain. It was really good
That's good
I'm gonna have a great day tomorrow. No matter what that's it man. Every day's a new day
I'm gonna make it happen
You move forward man, don't let anything get you down to the point where you just can't get up again
right well
And what I well not only because of what I've been through but also because of what I do I've learned how to
Which is kind of a gift in some sense, but to disassociate so why sometimes why I'm in the moment
You know I mean, it's like okay. This is you're feeling it. You know what I mean?
But like once that I get everything settled which today I finally got everybody safe. I got everybody settled so now I can kind of
Disassociate in a healthy way
So now I can just move on and do what I need to do otherwise
You know what I mean because I can't act what I because of what I do
I can't really sit and fill in so whole lot. You know what I mean? I could fill it for a couple days and then I
I go on you know not go on but you know what I mean
Yeah, you grieve when you can and you just keep doing what you got to do
Right. Yeah. Yes. In my world
She can be great and then she can just happen and it can be like that at rollercoaster
So, you know, you can't really afford to really sit and shit too long
It's amazing what you do man, you really do it really strong with that stuff
Yeah
Sometimes I don't know
but it gets done so that's all that matters and I love it you know it's just not every not every
week is hard like this week has been you know I mean I have really good weeks and it's really
amazing I could see a lot of amazing things and be a part of a lot of people's amazing journeys
but every so often there's weeks like this and it's just like shi-
Let's just keep it moving bounce you can found fucking well one day at a time man. That's one day at a time
That's saving the world. You're saving your own little piece of the world
And causing hell in the rest of it, that's right. That's what this is for
Yeah, it's got you gotta have an even balance, baby. You gotta have good and bad like how it's healthy
You can just come on here and be an evil fat bitch
All right, I'm gonna be an evil fat bitch
Yeah, I ain't saying like I'm everything, but yeah, I'm definitely an evil fat bitch. I
Love it
To show myself that way people can just think I'm some big fat as maybe I'll stop show myself
Just so people can't think I'm some big fat. No, no no shade to the to the big chicks
You know cuz hey, maybe it's all more cushion for the question, but I'll be quick
You know that. Oh, yeah
So I've been on here I've been on here for maybe like seven years right doing this bullshit here and there
I've come across so many evil fat bitches and my fucking rounds around this place
And when I say evil fat bitches, I'm talking about like miserable hateful cunts, you know
Yeah, they don't spew any kind of like fucking
Happiness or anything. They're just just continually spew hatred. It's just so fucking disgusting
It's like you're so down on your own life that this is all you got a fucking show
Even on this end you could decide to come here and fucking be a whole different person, but no you just rather be just a miserable cunt
Yeah
Don't get me wrong like I like being petty and I like talking my shit
But just to sit around and be like like that 24 I couldn't do that shit 24-7 like that's just I just don't see how anybody
You know what I mean? Because that's and that's why I
Do tip from time to time and yeah, just because I get busy or whatever
But I do appreciate those little breaks because I'm just like every now
Then you can get caught up in the argument and you know the blah blah blah, but again, I like
No, I'm trying I like a little I like a little mud wrestle every now and then. No, there has to be yeah, so here every now and then that's to be something
Yeah, you know and then have you know and then also have fun and you know because we have fun
We laugh we talk talk about serious. We roast and joke and that silly and and then yeah
Sometimes you know we crash the fuck out, but you know a good crash out's fun sometimes. I ain't gonna laugh
As long as you can pull yourself back from it and not dwell on it would the next day and see the same people and be like
Well, yeah, motherfucker. I heard what you said about me yesterday and last week in the year before that
Now motherfucker, don't carry that shit into the fucking day
This is a new fucking arena, you know, that's that's always my issue, right?
So I'll get into it with somebody or we'll have a back-and-forth and then me because usually I just don't give a fuck the next day
Or a couple of hours later. I really don't give a fuck, you know, because it is what it is. We're talking shit
Makes it, you know, motherfuckers
Like get the fuck over yourself, dude. Like, you know, like they hate that shit
They don't like they don't like it when we talk shit too fucking bad
Don't do stupid shit when nobody talks shit about you. That's not me. Exactly. Exactly. That's what we're here for
People talk shit about me. So fuck it. What I'll talk about shit back and didn't move the fuck on
There's hours and hours and hours of streams. Just people talking shit about me. You think I listen to them
I don't fucking listen to that shit. No
Fucking bullshit
Yep
God he did this shit again. God. He fucked up my whole fucking panel
Shut the fuck up
Summer's such a bitch. She's a fraud. She doesn't do anything. She's such a liar
No one that bitch laughs. She don't do nothing that bitch everybody hates her and her whole community hates her
That bitch don't do no work. She just rides around in her car
Love when they hate when they say everybody hates us. Fuck you with it with some of those to love people on here
What are they talking about? I know that's the funny part, right?
You hate me or hate me or not like me. I don't really give a fuck but guess what we don't have a good damn time
If you can get over yourself exactly
I
You know being from the Chicago, you know Chicago area, dude
That's everybody got fucking roasted if you didn't get roasted and have somebody talk to you
That was that was like a writer passage. What the fuck are you talking about?
That's how we were growing up, you know
Same shit nobody got mad because everybody said the same shit fuck you faggot fuck you asshole
You know, we didn't give a fuck what people said to us
Yeah
Everybody's got feelings
Oh, I thought he changed the screen off.
I was like, oh, are we in?
Oh, we're in the clouds.
It's not like a bad Sunday.
This is about time when he cuts the stream.
Psych, just let us know if you're gonna cut the stream,
if you wanna cut the stream, man, it's cool.
Just don't cut the stream on us without letting us know.
This dude doesn't like our conversation,
robot streamers, so yeah.
Yeah, it looks like you want you cut the screen about
Saying they are like that. Oh, no, we're I'm a complete asshole sweetie. Oh, yeah. Hey Joe wake everyone up. Yeah
What up summer
I actually expected to cuss like out now that sexy summer is here. I actually got a boner. Nice to meet you. No, I'm 300 pounds. I'm not sexy. No, you're not. You're 150 pounds of sexy. That's what you are. Well, I'm not 150 pounds either.
psyche I have to come back in something happened to my sound I'll be right back
let me right back up yeah I bet you will the reason I joined psyching because
beat is being very rude so what happened what happened oh I don't even want to
say you want me to say it I don't care if you want I don't care either way
I went up there looking for sex and being said, oh, Joe, you're this, that's not this and that.
I was like, really?
You know, I love you, baby.
She's like, yeah, I know you love me, but this and that.
I was like, really?
She's like, Joe, take her easy.
So I'm up here Ashley. I'm I actually want to come up and tell you go fuck yourselves like if you ever talk about my baby
Again, I'll kill every fucking one of you if you talk about my baby Peter
Oh, you want to do it? You want to play? Oh, Peter. Peter's a great person
You want to fight guys come on little punk you want to follow I'm looking for Joe. I want to fight all day
I didn't mean to say back in magnet magnet magnet
Well, you ding dong ding dong. Oh, there's this thing down there. Ding dong, the bitch is dead. Ding dong dong dong dong.
What were you saying before you misspoke?
Oh, I know
We're crashing out right now
Can we all do can't we all finna be friends instead of finna crash out is this a crash out?
Are we crashed out?
We're both fucking crash out. We might as well
Crash out. Come on. It's two in the morning guys crash out. You fucking losers. Oh
That's exactly the crash out
Speaking of D.Y. Ghost you crash out every fucking night like this ain't nothing new you always crash
Like two o'clock to do it though
Well, what can you repeat that in English? I
At least yes, sir. I can I can slow it down for you. I can use smaller words, too. I
Wait until two o'clock in the morning to do that
But yes
You know what I don't know about you go it's been about two months. Can you god give psyche a super chat for like $200 it's been a while
I don't know
You guys all ruin that shit
I can't even give him a dollar because you guys you guys are all gonna talk shit and say I'm trying to run
No, we're not gonna say nothing. Just so yo psyche when this package Joe shipply
N word again
the
Well, I don't think that necessarily was funny. I don't think coming up here breaking kills is funny
And you guys why'd you live in one funny? And why'd you live? I
Was laughing at something else. It wasn't funny. Then why'd you laugh? I
Was laughing at something else. Don't I mean how else do you?
Something else by the way, he was laughing at something else God something else by the way
Somebody knows. That was something else that made me laugh.
Listen, listen, before you guys do anything,
before you do your little thing, guys,
let's like you play a song.
I think it's Yanni.
Never got my reading by the way
Where's an Aquarius?
I am on Aquarius Moon.
January 7th.
It's Aquarius Moon. It's like actually Capricorn I'm born in, but it's like I'm Aquarius Moon.
Can you guess what I am? Go ahead please.
You?
Yeah.
I'm gonna say
Sagittarius.
I'll give you a hint, Simba.
So yeah, you're close like how do you have a fire sign? Oh
He's a fire sign
Motherfucking Leo. You're he's a Leo. Oh, I was just gonna say that
You weren't just gonna say that
By the way, it's like you didn't give me my animal do you still have that uh deck the animal?
Yeah
what do you want animal cookies well and you know God I could give you a reading
but I'd give you an animal reading if you want it's probably gonna come out dog
but I can I can pull one you know in a world of darkness the blind man is king
oh really now that's you pal so you when you here's what you got I goes got the
Fuck it says
Independent magical abundant
The cat is well known for its independent character in the Egyptian hierarchy of beasts
It was a supreme being the divine mother of all cats with the goddess fast as
depicted in this painting and first mother and deity of life and abundance the Greeks associated cats with the goddess Artemis
The huntress and virgin goddess of the moon the Roman version of Artemis was Diana who was known for witchcraft
And then the the Italian
Wasn't that in like Egyptian culture didn't they like worship cats in my room?
Well, yeah, but the Egyptians and the Romans were very similar because you know Alexander the great
They know xandria and stuff. So they're not fucking up after it. Don't forget that
Catholic cat Catholic, you know, we're a pastor God was she actually good look. I mean we can
Black cat's head
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Yeah
She's always the only ones
And by the way, she let's be honest. She's probably sleeping with all let's be honest. Let's just be all the way honest
I wouldn't have started a war over her
Helen oh, yeah, no, she was already married to somebody and so he like
The prince took her to Troy
Yeah, hell in Detroit, but yeah, but she she she had a husband. She's like her husband very much
So she wasn't like sad. Oh, yeah
She left and guess what he did he followed and guess what he did he brought his big brother and guess what he didn't brought the fucking
He brought all of everybody over there
Like that's my woman. Let's fight about it
Why what happened yeah, I didn't watch do they were they on?
Was watching Smackdown
WWE yeah, yeah, there's no on Netflix now
And I think it's over on Netflix. No, no, it's still on Netflix
Ross on Netflix. Yeah, that's right
Yeah, they do the live events and shit right smackdowns on regular TV and
Peacock just lost the ESPN ESPN is gonna start doing the live events
Peacock's not that big though. I mean
Yeah, I'm not an AJ Lee fan, I hate see I'm punk and I don't give a shit about AJ Lee honestly
So that didn't do shit
Lee I would DDT that motherfucker
AJ Lee's a girl
Wow, they're still getting fucking DDT. I don't give a fuck
Okay, I was wondering because how do you know about me blue?
What do you go? What do you say? Sorry goes. How do you know about Tiffany blue?
It was a color
How do you know that Tiffany blue part she needed the money like when you buy jewelry from there like doesn't it cut the box?
I think when I first learned about it was that movie believe it or not, but then
Who the fuck is that that's that God Leo Katra. She's in Tiffany blue
I think Tiffany blue is a really beautiful color
Well, yeah, but you watch some news stories. It's always showing up in some very strange news. Oh, it looks like one of those
avatars
Yeah
She's going to be in the next one, actually.
Hi.
Uh oh.
Sorry.
Aquarius Moon.
Here, you guys talk.
What the fuck you want to talk about?
Whoa, whoa, don't leave us alone.
Fuck it, let's talk.
What do you want to talk about?
Let's talk about the art of crashing out.
Wow, how do you figure that
you began your journey into crashing out?
Oh, many here, many moons, many Aquarius moons ago, yes.
Many moons ago, I once, Ghost was a young boy, he first crashed out.
First joined a panel, and it's been, you know, it's just been history and the making ever since then.
Party after party, right?
I wouldn't say party after party, but crash after crash.
How long has it been now for your Ghost, about four years, five years, you've been doing this?
Well, many many acquires. What was the queries moon? What is that one year? Yeah, why not?
Well many years ago about four or five. Yeah, that's my first crash I've happened
And it happened on the channel that I'm not gonna say
But it was a debate channel and I did a really good job and I fucking had to crash out because
They were gaslight and everything I had to crash out a little bit and you know, it just worked from there
And then after that, you know what happened was I typed an open panel and
I typed in a lot. You know, you got to click that live button
You know and I discovered people like God and Psyche and summer
And names we do not speak of
It's been a long it's been a long five years brother
Yeah, but you've been having a good time
Have I have I have have you have you been having a good time the best
Laughs more than I do
Like he's been on a roller coaster emotional roller coaster
That's what I showed up
And that's when we met God and you're so you I know you're so thankful to actually have met me and I'd be able to actually talk to me
I you know I I will say you're welcome, sir
No, you read my mind. I know I did I got you
Close your fucking car door by the way, that's too bad, you know, it's too bad we lost a lot of friends along the way though
Well, listen, we're here now though, and only the strong survive
Wrist in peace Alexander McQueen
All right P. Listen. So I keep burning a little something for his memorial. Is that uh, is that incense age?
I think it will say what's that after African burn?
Dragon's blade
I think like he probably would let him join if he agreed not to break to us, but I wouldn't trust that dude
Yeah, I'm pretty yeah, I think like I'm not gonna put words in psyche's mouth
I'm pretty sure he'd love to have him up here if he just didn't break deal as though
Oh, I'm I can fucking breathe that in psyche put that out man you fucking smother me to death incest. Yes smash
Nothing wrong with a little incest
You feel what compose you sir
That's looks good for you
No, yeah, yeah put it in the camera a little bit. Let me breathe that shit in. Oh, yeah. Oh
Yeah
I'm feeling good
You're the place is fucking smoking, huh? God you want me to say I'm finna crash out
Releasing spirit. Hey, you're gonna make some merch
T-shirt saying I'm finna crash out. No, let's go, you know, you know, you know what that would be a good idea
But I think the number one for me personally would be dumb dumb
That would be dumb dumb dumb's a great one that you write dumb dumb and then you put like an arrow
That one yeah, I'm with I'm with I don't know I can't really merge that because you go to New York everyone for that
And then I'll have I'll have a t-shirt that says God knows best
There we tell you right we're making money. I mean, I'm pretty sure it's not gonna get approved
But I agree with it. Nice. Why would it get approved? I mean that there's plenty of people to say
God knows best
God does know best or you know what I'm fully behind it. I retract my statement
The guy you don't need if somebody's on a fam God in the chat. Well, yes, who really cares
Well, you should have it you should have your own channel God though. I think don't you want me to leave?
My third one is let's run it
Let's run. I'm not a fan. Let's run it
All right, my bad. My bad. It's an herb. That's like an urban thing. You like my first two though
Yeah, crash also one of the best. Yeah, I like your you know God knows I like that one
Yeah, well robot you're gonna have to donate to the channel for that
At least you know what?
What's he want to do?
wants me to leave
well
You give 20 bucks up God will leave give 20 if you want to give 10 if you can't afford 20
I'll leave for 10 he'll leave for 10. He's been God is merciful sir with slash and prices
Why would you want God to leave he didn't do anything to you how rude doesn't matter what he wants
It's if you can make it happen or not ten dollars
Make it happen it's like post your cash out for him. Oh, there it is. It's at the banner
Yeah, ten bucks
And even though they take 80% of it
Yeah, the then it's like and also cash app is anonymous too, you know
And so if like, you know, you're concerned about the privacy or anything cash up to the monomist
It's just cash app dollar sign psyche awakens
Sin sin five dollars in and say let God stay, please
There you go, you just call me an abloviator I haven't said a fucking word
Are you
Should I not I don't think I should you better not yeah, fuck it. I'm reading it. Let's run it. Let's run once I
Was it a fucking word? What do you know damn?
You haven't shut up in an hour God. I could get a word in
It's been by the way, it's only been 48 minutes. You don't fuck I've been an hour
So if you really want to come up here you actually joined the fucking panel you want to run one let's do it
Those people don't come out coast. They just like to talk shit. Well, can I talk shit? Is that okay? God all day?
I'm finna crash out
By the way robot what kind of name is that?
You know, I'm saving I'm saving myself. Oh, no god. I'm saving myself. You know who I'm saving myself for in the chat
Who?
Jamie
Jamie's the best
Yeah, we're gonna run eventually we're gonna run one you can't say anything bad about Jamie ever
Well, listen, we're gonna run one. I'm not saying anything bad at all. I just run one. Yeah, I can see that
Yeah
Shit sometimes, you know, you might have a brother if you have a brother, you know order brother especially
I don't need your order brother, but there's been times where you had a
You had you had a fucking posting fish, you know, I'm saying you had a fight you had to run one
But guess what still your brother?
Well do this bitch riding a wolf
Yeah, that's that's not a wolf. That's a dire wolf. That's some kind of like miss. That's weird. That's like a weird
That's like a dire wolf. I ain't no fucking regular wolf. This is symbolism. Who's the girl and what's the
And Alaska they do get pretty big. They don't get that fucking big though
I think H8000 is going to AW I think he's just gonna retire
Dire wolf
Dire Wolf. I D I R E. Yeah. Look it up. I might do Google it because I might be miss. I might be miss
speaking. I know what a dire wolf is. Oh, okay. Hey, did they have those? Did they have those in Game of Thrones or
no? I didn't watch that shit after it ended. I didn't give a fuck. Yeah. Don't you mean the wolf? Do they have
the wolf on the show? The Dire Wolf. Yeah, they probably did. I didn't watch the whole show. I just
Six episodes
Hey, guess what we did if that was such a thing if they're actually one such thing as dire will guess what we did
We got pugs now brother. We got pugs now so many dire wolves
Yeah, yeah
You miniaturize all that shit
You know what actually there's certain dog breeds that actually you shouldn't even breed because like they have trouble breathing and like it's actually like
Kind of against their harm to actually breed them
I
You're gonna close your fucking work. Are you playing that music? Yeah, it's the wind chimes from the outside
Turn that shit off
Is it annoying you?
No, I'm just gonna fucking crash out about it. Then I just crushed up. Oh, yeah, I'm gonna crash
Gonna crash up on Jamie here Jamie hear that he's gonna crash out all over you
Yeah, she doesn't like it dude
I know
I'm gonna keep teasing as long as I'm live up here
I'm gonna tease the fuck out of it if Jamie was standing at the top of the stairs with you
She would push you down the stairs. Well, listen, you know what I would do
I would like I would literally jump down the stairs and you know what I would say I said she pushed me
No, she'd laugh and say yes, I did
You guys and she'd get charged with it and I would laugh when she was going to jail
Got you
We're the fucking psyche, why is he buttoning us up out here? We don't even like each other. Why are we talking?
Where's fucking psyche? We're waiting for a robot streamer to come up and fucking give us some intelligence. Oh
I guarantee it's not gonna be intelligent. Yeah
You're just gonna have to listen to this bullshit, then you know what? Here's my here's my here's my argument God real quick
I think there's actually a couple people that are actually really fucking intelligent in the chat
But they'll never fucking join the panel, but they're super fucking intelligent. Oh, yeah, that's
Me and you and like they're fucking intelligent, but they'll never fucking join well really smart people don't have to prove it
Exactly, that's that's a good point, but
That's a really good point, but they'll never join.
Yeah, you don't have to prove it or nothing,
but they'll never join.
Even though sometimes I think they feel like they want to,
I wonder why they don't.
Well, they don't feel comfortable. Some people don't want to have their voice heard. They don't want to talk on a panel
They're gonna be your voice. You don't have to show your picture. You don't have to do any of that
Well, that's what it's about the people that turn on their cameras
There's some people that turn on the camera and they show every fucking thing they'll show their asshole to you
But I think there's some people in here that are smart as fuck I
Think there's people that's listening don't even type in the chat. Believe it or not, and they're smart as fuck
I don't know. I'm not going. Yeah, there's tons of lurkers. Yeah. They use this like a TV show.
But you know what else? I say smart ones, but you know what else? This is lurking in the background.
It's the hate watchers. They're waiting for somebody to say something. I guarantee they're going to join
another panel. They're going to fucking his head all over it.
Almost crashed out. That was about that was about 20% you don't see me a hundred brother
Hey streamer if you want to hear psyche so bad, where is he?
What do you mean you want to hit him? What what do you want? He wants to hear his psyche speak?
He's here for like whoever it is. They're here for psyche to speak as you can see psyche's not here to speak
Get a wait until he comes back
Oh, look who showed up
Showed your face back around here
Let me see me she hasn't been back here what it's been two months
Are you talking about Slayer? Yeah
Slayer join the fucking panel. Come on up here you come on. Why are you hesitating?
She's shy robot by the way your argument
I can't fucking join the panel and argue with the fucking comments
So if you want to come up here and like run one, I'll do it with you. I
Can't have a full-out debate with you when you're in the comments. Just come up here and join
Yes, miss
You're very shy girl
Well, you don't have to be shy nobody's I won't disrespect you come up come up
No, we don't disrespect her
She's a yellow flower
She's a she's a she's a daisy if she does. Yeah, it's a very sweet daisy
I'm a huckleberry Tiger Lily
You know, maybe you know, God, maybe that's my fault. Maybe I should leave because I think sometimes I'm the problem
Anybody that they're like, oh, you're a debate. I don't want to debate. I just want to chill
But people think like well, obviously I will debate but they're thinking like oh, you're just like the debater
Like no one wants to talk to you like no one wants to join and it makes me feel bad when I join psyches because I feel like
I'm hurting them kind of
No, you know what it is ghost. It's the people like streamer
They come when they say they come here for psyche
They don't care if psyche says a word. They just want to watch his face on the panel
They just sits on the panel for like two hours. They don't watch him
I feel like God sometimes they don't want to join because of me because like they think I'm trying to debate them
Oh, you think you you make them feel insecure and stuff like that. Yeah, I think I think that comes off. Yeah
Cuz you have like superior intelligence
No, no, I'm fucking retarded by the way, and I'm not a debater
I'm fucking like them they feel like you know you're more smarter than they I don't know what you feel like that
I'll just say I'm fucking retarded obviously you could defeat me if you really want to but I don't even want to debate
I'm here to hang out
Need to calm down right now boy. You need to come to fuck
the
Mr.. Gary
Yeah, are you are you are you are ready to take a screenshot of my
You know, I did I'm ready to take a screen shot
What you did that why wouldn't I look at that you got cute
Can you wink again
Wait
Me no worries
Don't worry
How are you guys? Thank you. How are you?
Oh, we're doing fine, sweetie. So he's not here. Oh, thank you calling me a sweetie. Yeah, I'm a sweet spicy sour and
root
Ah
You're gonna apologize to you
There's nothing to
You kind of look like
You kind of look like a dumb dumb Joker, you know dumb dumb Joker me
I don't care whatever you're saying. I don't care. This is me. I'm not a fake. I'm not a catfish. I'm a real woman
You me show me a shirt show them what you're wearing
that's right. That's right. Hot cat, hot cat. That's right. Hot cat. That's right. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat. Hot cat.
You're done psyche you like I like the big round. I like the big round. It's a purple one of my favorite
Oh, you like the big one I'm fucking then you will definitely like me sweetheart
Purple yes purple like this purple like purple
put your hair up
Don't do it
At least this girl actually washes her hair. You can tell her hair is clean
I have my earrings
I have my earrings to go on
She uses prowl
Why is she using this fake?
I'm not from Kowloon. I'm not a lady boy
Nobody said that
I did not say that, I didn't say that
You, you're telling to Mr. Aldi
He never said that
You were a lady boy, you said that
I didn't say you were a lady boy
You called her a lady boy
I did not call you a lady boy
You said that my hair is a fake
That was a long time ago
No, no, no
It's about three months ago
Six months ago
Yeah
Good girl, you don't like this fucking place get the fuck out you fucking pig
Are you doing shit on this fucking stream?
Does a shit on the stream Hannah?
Hannah she comes in just shits on fucking psyches panel all the time get the fuck out of you
Go come up here miss Hannah
Yeah, come on up here with you fucking ugly fucker face.
Why the fuck is your face blue?
I told you, I am from Avatar movie.
What were you celebrating that movie for?
What did she just say?
Yeah, why are you celebrating?
Avatar movie, the blue, the blue people.
Avatar, Avatar, Avatar, Avatar, but I say Avatar.
But why were you celebrating it?
Mr. Fakie, where are you? How are you? Are you safe?
Yeah, how are you?
No, Mr. Fakie, is that you?
How do I look today, Mr. Fakie?
Leah Watson.
Oh, hello.
Hey, don't say that.
Where is he? Where is he?
Hi, there he is.
Mr. Fakie.
Alright, in the bottom?
What?
Hello.
How are you?
I did I this is a facial facial for a woman facial face because I have a two days off so I did for the three times
You have pimples. You have every day off. You have pimples. Two days. Two days. Friday and Saturday.
Why are you celebrating the movie? Huh? Why is your face blue? Why are you celebrating the movie?
You just don't agree. What start attack that poor lady. Oh my god
She's a beautiful woman
She's top five
Hey god
Ah yeah, why do you
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
I cannot even speak Chinese.
Do you think I'm real good at speaking Chinese?
She loves the taste. It's big Chinese. Okay. Um, what is it? Um
That was good
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank
I thought I'd come up here to confuse Hannah because according to Hannah, me and God here, damn, you're the same person.
Who gives a fuck what Hannah says? She's almost dead anyway.
Oh, yeah! Come on, that's not what you're talking about!
Bash reminds me of God here, okay.
Mr. Goddy!
Hannah's a clown.
Yes, you me. You me, yes. Speak to me.
I can see you.
I think
Open your mouth. Yo, I have a question for you. Yeah
You remember when we asked her to speak like Chinese or wherever she's from you remember she has to do she didn't even speak it
Yeah, you're right. You're right. You're not even fucking speaker, man. You're right. She's a fake Chinese
I hope we don't talk too much.
You guys hate me? Really?
They're real shiny!
That guy can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can come, he can
Oh, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look at that, look
To be honest
Joe you enjoy the whole
Your card
But yeah, I bet you are one too.
Uh, Pachu, Pachu larger dance, the, the, the, the, the, yeah, you know, it's not cool, yeah, I know that.
Melanie, who's that?
Ya, itu daripada Indonesia.
Patura untuk berjalan.
Ilnana you got the Ilnana
I'm sleeping right now
Yeah, it's in town. Roman cooks popcorn with chippy pop it pop that shit pop it pop that
Melly Melly Mikey yeah, you're rich and black with the patch you larger than
How do you say, how do you uh, guys, real quick in the comments, you are not that one, not that one, not that one, how do you say shut the fuck up in Chinese and we beg thy blessings right now, Vince Conez is redefining new, I don't know, I am not at all, Vince is a, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know
This feels so dirty playing a rumble video on YouTube
Yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Yes, yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes
I'm being disgusting right now.
What are you talking about?
That sounds like her sex life, Gotti.
Yes, she did.
You know I'm going to hear about her sex life.
I wish.
I'm not talking about my sex life, Cody.
Look at that.
I'm cracking out right now.
What do you think? She's wearing blackface.
What do you think?
Yeah, that's a full black base.
This is the gray, gray, gray, gray.
That's even worse.
Blue?
Even worse.
Gray is worse.
Disgusting.
Yeah, whatever.
You're making fun of Ash.
Disgusting.
Disgusting, yes.
It's good for the game.
You're making fun of course.
I know, right?
It's good for the game.
You're making fun
Because because this is psyche is okay, okay because mr. Psychi is okay, and he's fine
Okay
He is okay. That's a gay guy you're talking about. Yeah, that's rude. There you call a gay guy gay. What's wrong with you?
Don't lie. Don't lie. Are you guys deaf?
I'll try to guess like us.
Are you guys deaf? People, I said okay.
So what? So what if Mr. Scythian is gay or what?
I'm okay with that.
But you're always nice to me, so what?
Hey, God, he does your mind. You have missed one.
You guys are deaf.
No, but I'm thinking about the director.
Thank God.
You're going to crash.
Including me.
See your mind.
Something wrong with your ear.
This one for mad TV. I
Haven't seen it a long time. Oh my god. You haven't seen miss one. All right. Do you got some research to do?
Somebody crash out
Yeah, that's black Archie
Fuckin blue-flate blue face. What are you gonna crit walkers?
You don't like black
Tired of you don't understand English
You don't know what the fuck I'm talking about do you explain please explain what I just said blue man chew
that
You blow me a kiss and I'll tell you, stop being pervert, stop being pervert, Ms. Goddy, stop, you know you want to do it, just tell me your tips and I'll tell you, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
it's no
oh boy, alright, alright
breathe from you, Mr. Gotti
breathe from your game, Mr. Gotti
are you still with that guy?
I still like and respect you, Mr. Gotti
but it doesn't mean that
that's right, you do
Leave her alone. I still like and respect you. It doesn't mean that I will give you bad things with you
Why is that bad? And it doesn't mean that I
Listen to any favor that you say to me. No, it's not. That's not me
Listen, you showed me your underwear. We're only way past that. We're way past that. You showed me your underwear in private, remember?
Shamuta underwear. It's just underwear not my naked body
Yeah, but you don't even wear underwear so the joke's on you
The burden of
You may claim the burden of proof on you. How are you not blue go ahead?
It's a rain now. I gotta go off. Bye. Bye
Where you go
You're okay. You're okay. Thank you for letting me off with these perfect people. He wants to kick us off so bad.
He's a pervert.
He's looking for work as a gist.
That's Goddy right there.
That was kind of doggy.
That was like doggy.
No, that looked like psyching it.
Hold on.
Oh, this guy.
He's your asshole.
This is a new story.
Look, the ladies.
This is definitely a true story.
There you go
Look at his psyched freaking skull!
Look at his freaking psychic!
Look at his smile, bro!
What a weirdo!
Are you bringing this kid to the wrong place?
We're dead.
Boris, you're found a way to make the 10th pass up to here.
He's got the body of a 12-year-old.
Look at that!
Wake him up!
I have to see my wear on my shirt.
Holy shit!
You have no idea, man.
Holy fuck it.
Oh, that's late.
Because you can't fix it.
You gotta stand.
I wish I knew how to quit you.
I'll kiss you as well.
I like the way, I like the way that the psyche is smiling.
Like that.
I'm the queen of the world.
This could be real.
I'm the king of the world.
What's our body beat on the king of the road?
Like you are you looking hella dreamy-eyed right now man. I don't see psyche this and love since that other guy came up here
The one
Like you have a sparkle in his eyes
I
Know this nightbot's out of fucking control
She did. She's back with her face.
That would be very much.
You really just cammed out some milk duds, dude?
I just cammed out the shit of you guys,
the fucking milk dud.
Yumi, what happened to your glasses?
I don't wear your glasses anymore.
When I showed up the milk dud, I was like,
this is sand man with eyes.
I'm Yumi.
Where are your glasses?
Oh, okay.
My milk dud just said,
shoo-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee.
Oh, my glasses?
Yeah, where are your glasses?
it's here
why
put them on, put them on real quick
oh wait
I'm putting so much on you
can I draw you like one of my thumbs girl
she really needs a cam down to put on her glasses
she's gonna put them on
I just wanna draw like one of my thumbs girls
she loves me, she does whatever I say
I would speed up, I would speed up X-ray glasses
or she could see me naked
back. Yeah. Very much. I don't
put our naked glasses on Bita.
When you put them on, you can
look at that. Look at that.
Look at that. Look at that.
This is my new backpack.
My backpack.
There you go guys show it. I think you just showed this fucking shlong
She says she's not a lady boy. That's a koojee bag. I want a camera
I
Are you showing a victory secret again, I really kill you really
Put on your grass
You can't see you see this and you put your glass and so it is to this middle
finger.
That was weird.
That was actually weird.
No, no.
Put them on your face.
But wait a second.
Wait.
That's my face.
That's on your face.
Oh my God.
How long do I got to wait?
This fucking hard one's not gonna last forever
There we go, there we go beautiful beautiful
That's okay, you're not a catfish
I'm not a catfish. No, I'm not
Thank you, baby. We'll look about not a catfish
You know like that is the catfish
What what I'm not a catfish
I'm not a catfish
You might not be anything after the guy I gotta go. Where you going?
I have my family
No, no, I'm not happy you're happy. No
You're really happy. They know the three hours
When I see when I see you I light up like this
I
Tell you one thing even like this even like the 90% of the bitches on this fucking shit
Exactly, but there's only like five
No
Yeah, as long as you me stays up here, we're gonna be up here
Now fuck you
So hot that's so fucking hot you too. I came for I came here
Hello? Hello? Are you making Chinese eyes? Are you making Chinese eyes? Do the other one too.
Is it who's this who's mr. Swan who's that?
Oh my god somebody got jealous of you me and came up here
That's that other dude
That's that's that's that's
that's that's that's that's
That's you
He's doing an impression of India
Kid rock
You me impression
Oh, hello.
Yo, dude, you're from India.
You look like someone from India.
I'm going to ask, I'm going to ask
where you got that apron from.
Acha, acha, Americae.
That's the swan for the tea.
Who was that?
You know what I'll do.
You know what I'll do?
You had your chance.
Lovely Indian dude for a fun way there.
Oh, is that a cow?
Is that your god, a cow?
Yeah, it's your chance.
We're just pretty boon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-jabboon-j
Stop teasing me. Mr. Gotti. I kill you. Oh, I will say it. The shark. Oh, Avatar. Avatar. Don't
threaten him with a good time. It's the voice. What voice? I'm using my phone. I don't I don't
even know what was that. Oh, hello, Mr. Gotti. Can you can you come closer? Miss or Mr.
Can I see your face? Can you come closer?
Not your hair, your face.
Give me that catfish, that's a catfish.
I got closer for you, me.
Oh, hello.
Hello, how cool am I to talk to you?
And God told me to say that by the way, it wasn't me.
Miss be da is is that miss be da? No, it's not
Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my
God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh
Yes, it is you have a long time like
Classic I thought we were friends, you mean oh
Shit, this is a little too good. He's gonna get an award for this one
You got to go to work that fucking apron is amazing dude
I can't see you up there. Can you put it in the middle?
Tell me you didn't cut up your tablecloth to make that apron, dude.
Yeah, I love it.
Call me Tony.
Is that Mr. Alex though?
Hey, you might have cut us off. How long do we got?
You did cut us off.
Yo, man, you put a fake a boob. I knew it. Yo, man, you put a fake boob. She's not even the real boob
But show them show him real boob
No, thank you, mr. Gotti you have Santa Claus. It's hiding. Yep. You haven't changed
Christmas. I hate to know what the sock smells like
That's his girlfriend.
Probably smells like Old Spice and Sweat.
Leave the sock alone.
Miss Juan, Miss Juan, is that Miss Juan?
I can't even read the name.
I don't wear my glasses.
That's Black Swan. That's Black Swan.
Well, I gotta be Black for her.
No, it's not. That's not her.
That's not her.
Yeah, what the fuck, bro?
Is that Mr. Swan?
You know who me?
Can you dance, Miss Juan?
dance for me. Miss one. Can
you dance? I dance for you.
You dance. I do the elbow dance.
You know, that's the ugly dance.
You should dance like that.
Show how it's done.
But you should like that.
Oh, he's dead
Can't believe what this is like I'm so sorry for doing this. It's your fault
What have you created? I always like and respect Mrs. Mikey, but I I stay away from
history for
Why please dance
This dance, would you dance?
Oh my god, my eyes.
Okay, a recipe.
He stopped.
She said recipe.
Did she leave this isn't cool now that she left
Nick you're gonna have to take over let's change who your best human impression
Well, there she is oh my god, thank God
Where did he go?
He's doing a Yumi impression Yumi looks just like you
How do I do it? Do you want me to bring me?
I'm crazy? No I'm not
I'm doing fashion
I'm doing fashion with my face
I'm not crazy
She's doing fashion too
You're me
I'm not from Middle East
It's like twins
Are you mocking someone from Middle East?
You
Not me
I'm Indonesian
He has the same face
Don't be right this look you guys calling me a rat
What's a racist
With people don't make fun it's not even funny
Are you sure but she likes white rice though
Oh who doesn't yeah
That's black Archie no
Yes, I recognize your voice I recognize your voice you don't recognize you don't recognize nothing
Yeah, are you done? Are you done being rude to me? No
Ever do that
I don't know. I don't know why
I don't know why Mr. R. D.
always always always always
always always appear when I
always appear when I show up.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
Put it on my you're not you you you you you doesn't look like someone from Middle East, but you more look like from India
What are you gonna do today you're gonna go have a picnic
Yumi picnic no the fam
Picking a shot take a shower of my child
Okay, I guess that's okay over there
Any last any last word? Yes, I love you so much
I don't love you mr. Gotti. I hate you. That's okay. I don't care
I don't care. I love you. I love you so much
No, I'm just kidding. We're gonna give you a ride mr. Gotti beautiful. Yeah, like we're like a common daddy. Yeah, that's a beautiful day
Have a beautiful day
Just call me daddy
She did I heard that no
Have a beautiful day for you guys
You guys fill up and it was late. Oh you me before you go. Can you cash out?
$5
Can you send Psyche back or whatever currency it is over there in your area of the world?
We can, well, I can give Mr. Psyche $5 for, like, I don't know, buy him...
Indonesian dinner from from from maybe breakfast or
Wait for it
You like Starbucks Starbucks no Starbucks
Starbucks is support is
Love when she does that how long do you think you have to wait for the money?
That's a phallic
Hi miss phallic
Phallic or phallic?
Oh you said phallic?
Phallic is a weirdo
Swan's trying so hard to smoke right now
Look at this struggle. It's like how long we got two minutes. No
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you, mr.
Mr. Psyche and mr. Gotti and for you mr. Black RG
I'm not RG god damn it. Thank you for coming. You're the best read
Read the screen. Don't forget to make me dinner
Your voice your voice it's a
No, no, that's that's
I was gonna call you I was gonna call you over and another cat. That's an insult
Yeah, for me it's an insult. I know
You know me enemies I have to you don't want to be called me
Oh
Two more hours damp psych. It's a long time
Ten more minutes left ten minutes left everybody get your fucking shots in right now
You know you might as well stay
He's gonna shut the he's gonna shut the whole shit down in 10 minutes. So you might as well stay
He's gonna get some sleep anyway
Yeah, baby, yeah, what do I look like do I look like that that evil?
No
Beautiful angel
Okay, I'm out of here. Thank you. What this is another 10 minutes. No
Don't leave me up here minutes
Don't leave me alone. Please leave me alone. Please don't go. Please don't go. Please don't go. I remember the old song. Please don't go. No, no, no, no, no. Where do you go? My love is where do you go?
I want to know. I want to know. Where do you go? Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh.
my lovely where do you go I want to know oh I wasn't bored I wasn't bored but
that's all I don't know where I am
Gawisha Malak
Gawisha?
Dracula, Dracula
Dracula
Oh, oh, oh, oh, Mr. Psyche
Do you have, do you have, do you have Netflix?
Do you have Netflix, Netflix?
No, I don't, I don't
Are you guys using Netflix?
Um, who are-
You know what the hardest the hardest the hardest Netflix character in
2025 is goes to Lord Morpheus. It is the Lord Morpheus. King of Dreams.
You saw what? Yeah, he's so hot
Sadly
Go take a shower
Bye
Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Don't forget to write. Don't forget to write. Bye-bye
That's because I was up here
God, oh, I have a song to play and I'll keep it. I'll hit the panel for extra five minutes. All right, cool
This is my favorite
What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What
Here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go,
here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go,
Working. Oh, no, I'm out of pilot. Oh my god, you know who he is right now
That's Sam. Oh, it's a man. Yeah, let's say salmon. He does look like salmon. Oh
Come on. That's okay. He does
He doesn't you me just did right, okay, I think this is it
Enjoy guys
She whispers in flames
Plays hide and seek with the shadows and nails
Turns every ar-
I need a ball hit.
that was beautiful. That was so beautiful. Wow. I cared about it.
What's good is that it's actually in my placement, astrologically. It's actually a song that's
like about the temperament placement a little bit. Kind of, you know, I would consider the
onima because it's like the darkest. You liked it? Oh, I always smile like that.
It's like what do you see yourself as you see yourself as like a devil type character or like a demon
Well, I do have a thing for little so you see yourself as a lily then
Yeah
I think but I have lily's in Scorpio and it's like in my house of reputation and while you're drawn to Lilith
Cuz she's into demons and stuff
They dream about
So you think you're in another life. Oh like a like
Something that it's like inside of every man, but man always will project that onto women, you know, and like
his women can kind of like reach like kind of like absorb like
They're really good at about returning into a mirror a little bit of like a man's own psyche
And so it's like
Eternal powers
projecting them out because they can project them out like that's been for
healthcare
they got poisonous or with swords in there
they're ladyfights or whatever
That's too deep man, you're getting too deep with it
That's not getting too deep, this is actually, Carl Jung is a theory about the anima
Oh the anima, yeah I heard about that the other day you were reading it
Yeah
I mean, yeah, so you say you were going to play with Carl Jung, he's like a German, you know, a German father of, basically, he's had a significant pride in who he also knew, and they had a lot of disagreements.
Yeah, he was probably one of the fathers of farmers, I think.
So you went to Freud and Einstein used to always debate about that stuff.
Yeah, I know, well, he actually had a fight with Carl Jung and everything, because I think he thought, the Carl Jung kind of thought,
Okay, so we have uh, you know who hated you hated statement Freud is this Nietzsche
Hello
That's Vader
Oh
Just respect the panel that's all
You can make your medication this morning speaking English
What happened to your teeth
Don't take them away from me. I'll sell them back to you for 20 bucks
For the bargain
I'll see you at midnight, we'll see you at midnight, at midnight if someone donates
Within like now at midnight. What do you mean midnight? It's 12 it's 12 47 where you are. Oh, hold on
Oh my gosh now one in the morning. I'm sorry
We're going another 10 minutes then. Yeah. Yeah
And unless somebody wants to donate, I'll give them to you.
Yeah, I've chosen one.
I want to see if there's a way I can end on standby, that's all.
Darryl, you're going to donate to the channel, Darryl?
You're going to have to pay for it.
I don't have any money, man.
I live humbly.
OK.
You got a couple quid stashed away.
100 matches and all that.
There you go.
We know where you hide it.
That's where Mrs. keeps it.
Did you chop them though, just in case?
How was your day?
Yeah, I don't understand me.
Have you opened up your shirt?
I'm going to tell the general.
God bless you, Darrell, God bless you.
Oh, he left? What did he say?
I hope you find the teeth.
He said something about going to find some teeth and God bless.
I wish him luck. Yep, okay, I know they have
I think you had a stroke his speech was off
Hey, God, so you want to see me fine? Yeah, of course, I'm always down for a laugh
Better not be my docks no
Hold on
Bye-bye always smile. Oh
You're leaving. Okay. Thank you. Thank you for coming come back again. I hope you have I hope you have fun
And Drophonies and Drophonies I
Like them gorgeous pretty booty nail salon
Let's see, let's see, let's see, yeah this is on my show I think, my crystals are too,
okay, I'll try this out, um, sure, okay, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see,
six years old my memory feels as sharp as it did in my 20s so it's nice to get it loaded it may
be menopause belly welcome to menopause a slower metabolism okay okay was that it
this blogger guy's a weirdo man of all the fucking weirdos on here this blogger guy's one of the weirdest
He's got a hard on for you psych honestly. I think he's trying to steal your look too
Is this the funny part
Hello
Hello, hello, Mrs. Swan, hello, hello, Mrs. Swan, hello, can you hear me?
I think what happened to me or the dog compared to a ham no no no no compare what he did was
public information that was already out there
He put out there. Yeah. So you'll beat us there. Beat us. Share my stream real quick. Be the please like don't don't even like
I don't know what it is. Although it's just a website or anything. It ain't it ain't. Now you calling it Doxon. Now you calling it Doxon.
I'm not. I don't know what website. I'm not going to put out any.
You're making me scared. Yeah, exactly baby.
No, I'm not. I don't condone it. I don't do it. I don't. It's not on my channel. I'm not doing any of that.
It's your website. I am not putting anything out there that's going to expose anybody. It ain't.
Worst enemy, but I won't call it when it's fucking clear
How you gonna call it not doxing but you scared the fucking show website
What is it? Tell me what it is. Give me a summary. It's showing you right there. I can't see it, explain it to me before I put it on the screen.
What was funny about that? Nothing was funny. I was like, I thought it was funny.
I was waiting for the punchline. Oh
Pissed crazy off crazy when today just now
You did some of the church he's pissed that she left
Face I think you should come up here and let him know personally how you feel
Don't keep it inside because it's only gonna eat you alive
Come up on the panel let him hear your distress
Now the party started
We only have five minutes left anyway
Okay, I'm fucking special it's fucking five minutes to four
I thought I thought Nick was an impression of you
I don't want to be known that I'm in the bar the last thing I do it open my mouth
Holy shit, you know as long as I shut up like it's in there all fucking day
But the minute they hear me talk, I know who it is
I don't know. I don't know.
That's you see he thinks he's the devil. I knew it. He thinks he's your fucking devil boys
That's why I'm here to fuck. That's why I'm here to fuck with you
That's why I'm here to fuck with him. Yeah
That's why I'm fucking with your brain boy cuz you think you're the devil
Fucking devil you're not the devil
You're not the devil
I believe
You're just an insecure little guy who lives by the
We know a joke when we hear one
That's great. It's great because he can't take a joke. I love it
Well, he's a little pissy here. Yeah a little. Yeah
Well because the moon is in Pisces right now and he's not happy about that
Well, I'm gonna be 60 and it'll be soon be in Virgo. Oh
Talks almost paid for
Where you going I'm going to Virginia. Oh, Virginia's nice I go in the mountains over by Kentucky. Oh very nice
That's where Cecil's from you can make moonshine over there. Yeah, we got a family recipe
Take care, Leia.
Bye, Leia. Thank you for being here.
You like this guy? Tracy, what do you think?
That's good.
What guy?
That's good. That's better than the devil, yeah.
Hey!
Is that the Archangel one you did?
No, this is one that I just asked of.
Angel thought I was
He said
Something or
That's dude like green like the world and like and like the devil ones about like kind of like
Is do as I will
You know funny if you start eating food and working out and doing steroids you'll look like this guy
I know
We'll make a man out of you. Yes, like come on
I'm not really searching for anything.
But the photos was animation thing and it's like it's kind of like you don't know what it's gonna come out as but it's so it's a green screen you got
Well, yeah, that's all that on this on the stream yard. This is just my background. But yeah, I have a green street right there
Yeah, that's my house. I never figured it shit out. I was like ice not that important
Okay, so you like rock music like it just if you like this and I didn't have any
Disturbed right now down with the sick
Well, that's good. That's pretty good here, but I can't I can't it's just got the words up on it
That's about heroin right I
Guess so
I would say down when the sickness would be here. I did I did edit all this together too. Yeah, you did heroin spike
Oh, okay. I
When did you get off it?
I'm not a heroine and never have anything. Oh, I love her. I used to love her
Good stuff
What's this shit? Oh, oh my god. She's hot
Not
It's a great
She rises in shadows
Oh, he's a banger of shit now
And strong
Lilith in Scorpio
My anima flame
Christmas, my secrets
Calls out my name
Here you go, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
That's it.
That bill is familiar.
That's Emma.
Yeah, definitely.
That's it
Bravo Bravo
I'll still go
I love you
Yeah
Thank you, thank you. That was great man. You did you made that whole thing yourself. Yep
That's right, you're cool, you have been really bored.
Wow.
Well, I can understand pretty much what you're saying.
Did you have to pay for that?
Yeah, well, some of the things are,
yeah, there's mostly services that I put for you out there,
but you can do it for free.
Maybe you can do these things for free.
There's a lot of trial available and things like that.
There's a lot of different types of software out there.
You just have to test them out,
like there's some that are really,
Good and like some that are like really terrible. I mean, it's like it's so it's like yeah, it's about it's like
those tests and that's something that we do different small animations and
About a theme I can put them together in the video
video with music and I was like, I really like put a lot of work
Images and stuff like that
I want to take an online class for AI.
I'm doing it right now.
I'm doing some big comp and engineering classes.
I'm doing a bunch of them.
Yeah, holy shit.
Yeah.
I really uh, I do get seriously a lot more like than just like always like does everything for you is like if you can like
Like it's not very something we'll just do it will like
But it's like if you get to know it and talk to it and then like also tell it
This is what you want and like exactly and then you say then you keep refining it
And it's like you're not gonna always gonna come out right and you can always tell it like
But like just how to change it and stuff like that. So it's like really
So it's a tips of technology I'm waiting for because it's everything else is like too complicated for me really
I'm a simple person. I think it's a lot of words where it's like my I think my dad was too like he like always used like just like
everything on paper, you know, it's like
Never use a computer ever, you know
Just use that first like
business and so, what are you showing, Nick?
Oh, no.
Nice.
I'm in the sixties.
Yeah, I was in the sixty-five.
That's the best fucking rate.
Nineteen sixty-five?
Yeah.
What happened that year?
Uh, we had a war.
Beatles.
Uh, Beatles came out before I was born.
I did one more in 1962, 1963.
Were they that early?
Oh, they came to the U.S. in 65.
That's what I was thinking about.
Um, I think they did, they had celled and celled.
In 65?
Yeah.
In 69 I
Can remember seeing that on television the moon landing. Yeah, it was a good movie
Movie, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, exactly. No, yeah
How did it look on the TV when you watched it like I'm like a lot of it was black and white
You can't have a color TV yet. Well, I mean it's a black and white thing and the footage too. I mean, it's like
It wasn't that grainy
Did you have a big TV I
Was a floor model that would just be kids on each side
It was like it was a piece of furniture television wasn't just
I tell them it was a piece of furniture back there made out of wood. Yeah. Yeah fucking heavy, too
It would work better when the tubes were hot, yeah
Yeah, it damn sure would and it had a big fucking tube coming out of it god damn it quit flicking shit, would you
God damn it. You do that to me every time you move me all over the place, and you flick
I'd be next to a black guy
I'm not black. What a way to give a fuck. Oh look in that spectre picture
Great, let's go. I'm so fatigued with your motherfuckers
Jesus Christ when they learn how to act your fucking public I'll treat him
He thinks just because you're from Dorchester that he thinks you're racist. No, no Dorchester. Jesus Christ
I'm like really mad and it's a really good tip for me, but
Everyone's on stream yard, right? Are you guys on stream or do you have stream art Tracy?
Or do you use that? Why are you streaming? Yeah, I just came yeah
You know
Well, here's a tip and it's like and it's like sometimes it takes months to find out fine things and it's like just because I want to help everybody
I'm not trying to compete with anybody. I just want everyone to know
Okay, so stream yard
You know it records like 50 hours. I think if you're upgraded
Yeah, but when you put but for I'm I'm I'm upgraded, you know, I'm also on a discounted rating stuff like that
You're paying about $250 a year
It's expensive. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah, definitely at least that because I I was
Like I cancel it went to 25 bucks
It's I get for 25 for what he does for what he does
Yeah, if you buy it for you. Yeah, I mean, but I don't like I guess it's like
Oh, you saved your fucking money up and you go boom there it is
And you know everybody's a big expense. It's a big you can't save money. I can't go to my big fingers
Yeah, you you use that card like it's liquid there
Well, I mean, it's like I just just in this eating food and like, you know, I've been sick, but I go to McDonald's
What? Yeah, I got this McDonald's. I got this for free. Okay, then I got like, what else do I get?
I got like a regular coffee, so I feel like three or three or something
for like two coffees and a balance.
And so that's-
For the price that you spend,
you can get you a damn $18 coffee pot
and buy goddamn a big thing of coffee
and you could drink for a month for under 20 bucks.
But I wanna wrap it up.
Yeah, it's not a fault, it's just crystals.
And I didn't want to walk too, and so it's just for $3 just to take like a walk
Yeah, it's just $3, but you keep adding them $3 together and you just bought a coffee bar
I just bought a coffee bar. I used to get Starbucks. Now it's like Starbucks is a waste, right?
Starbucks is way too expensive. Why would you drink anything else but what you make? How do you know somebody spit in that shit?
Oh, they don't spit in the coffee the first. Oh, yeah
Yep
Your white oh see
Of course that's been two times
Hey, there's a black guy sitting on panel
of the
Yeah, they're real. They're not even real or I mean it's a photograph. Oh, it's a photograph real fucking people
God, are you back in the sea left?
That's not me psyche that guy's not me he's been up in the whole
That's not me I'm telling you
She's just crazy
You don't listen he's been up here for four hours, it's not me
By the way, I generated all these images like
Amazing
I can't do this shit. I have no fucking give fuck somebody you got a patience for that shit
Yeah, you got a tweak in all that stuff
Got a fucking rebuild the carburetor with the old man fucking tomorrow on that fucking 63 van
Just having I do it. I got it's been sitting for two years because I fucking never got ties on it
Did you ties on it? I finally got ties on it. So I give the inspection sticker
It's a fucking brand new carburetor, but it's been sitting for two years and the fucking things leaking the goddamn gas gets dissolved on it
So the old man bought a carburetor kit, so we're gonna go take it apart tomorrow and soak it in fucking acid for about 24 hours.
And then we got a carburetor kit. I already bought it. I gave him 100 bucks. I said go get a kit.
Tracy you're really mad at me with or in the child I'm mad at you. I'm up here. Why would I why do you always have so much best to you?
No, I said you said what he had a bullshit I came here to have fun and drink a fucking beer
And smoke some windows and shit, and I'm hearing fucking bitchin
And I'm like, well, fuck is it be good if I don't want to hear about you bitches, what I'm fucking drinking
Sorry, we're being a good move. I don't want to fucking listen to the bullshit
Why do you pay attention
She'll burn out
She'll do enough freak-offs where she ain't doing nothing new. They'll find another bride begging her and then they'll all go their way
She'll burn out. They usually do
Usually takes about a year or two
They do
Brides like that they hit it right because they got to hate
They got to hate and people like to hate nowadays because they're not happy with the fucking world
Well, it was funny, you know
She was like, oh, I don't want to talk about psyche but then she kept talking about me over and it's like a wall. Then why are you watching?
Exactly. Oh, I was I was just told by somebody. Oh, why do you listen?
Be done with it. I'm done the word done done
But yeah, she's acting like I'm like acting obsessed about or something about her
Like I'm not
Oh, he was the same with Emma, and it's like yes
I played this role where I'm like pretending to love the drama
Yeah, well just with those I do that kind of just to poke I don't know but it's like
Feel like you fall apart if you lose the drama in your channel
You're going to hit rock. You're
going to hit rock. I've already
hit rock bottom. You're going to
get sick of hearing the same
shit over and over. Well, they're
not hearing the same shit over
and over. That's why I'm doing
the different. No, I'm talking
about their channels. I don't
need to say their names anymore.
Okay, I got you. You know what
I mean? Their channels are going
to bottom out. They always do.
The hate is going to get
repetitive and people are going
Repetition yeah, I fucking can't stand the repetition and people burn out on it where you're gonna advance
People will come back to you like I did
Say hey, he's more the life than this shit
I got enough bullshit on the streets to listen to with the fatigue everywhere
Comes in all fucking colors
Jesus I've seen some assholes out there
I do, I do fucking look at them like I'm gonna fucking stick them with my eyes.
Get out of god damn way.
You can't buy shit and go, then you can fuck up whatever you want.
Well, you know, I mean, it's really nice to have, you know, people like, and you enjoy my show.
It's like, it's like cool to have people that like, you know, I know a lot of people do like, enjoy the show and stuff like that.
It's not just not me. It's like a lot of people like there's like a lot of great people that are right
It's in the show in the chat and on the show and there's a lot of people that aren't here anymore
like you know, both like you know physically and also just like on their own or on their own accord, you know, but
We do have like a lot of people that are just like have been here for months and much and I just want to thank everybody
for continuing to
Tune in I used to come here for the brats, but you ran them all off
Well, you know the broads were giving off free fuck. I mean, I ran them off
All the good ones
No, I wasn't part of that. I said the good ones. I said the good ones
Do you mean there is good ones? There's two or three. Is that really? Yeah, there are you gonna know where to look
I remember I got that idea before the one in the freak off when it first started and then the next morning I heard about it and I was like what I was so glad I thought fuck you went to bed that night I was like fuck I see myself so much bullshit
people were sending me clips from the freak off and I'm like
And I had to turn my phone upside down to see one of them.
I was like, what the fuck is going on?
This broad's upside down.
Leg spread with the feet up on the back of the chair.
Or down with who?
Quad unfolded and I'm going.
I can't help it, Janet did.
No, I'm talking about beat up.
Oh, beat up.
Oh my god, I went, what the fuck?
And then I've heard about fucking her fucking Lincoln is sucking a dildo and I'm like from Tommy and I'm like
I can't do it
No
The I what did to that cake in the 70s? I damn sure ain't into it now
When it comes to rubber and plastic and toys shit, I'm out
Sorry you missed it all there
It's all right, I'll catch the next one
Oh, they're always been there's always one popping off
Why you're queer I know we can go to like a gay gay bar
I would go to a fucking gay bar with you. I would have all five gay strip joints are my favorite
Oh my god, the men all over the fucking place don't have to worry about touching no more than touching me
It's all the fuck. I had a ball because you know, the Sun's clear
And he was a drag queen back then they used to do it in the strip clubs
the drag queen shit I
Was in the fucking 90s. I guess
40 he's your age 44
Uh-huh
You were having him my mom was having me and like I was in Charlotte Memorial Hospital having him
Uh, yeah, so yeah, but if we had any differences like we're I'm glad we were able to come back together
No differences with you. I just like the fact that you want to fucking make some mingle with people that are fucking nasty and do mean shit
And I knew it was gonna backfire. He's gonna bite you with the ass and I kept sitting there watching and finally I couldn't watch it
Don't walk because you know when you like somebody you won't see it go down
Wow, look at that smell. That's a lot of smoke from a babe.
Yeah, well, thank you for like, you know, give me a hug.
Oh, and you gotta hold me. I was fucking flabbergasted. I was like, who the fuck, sis?
Ha ha ha ha, what the fuck?
Yeah.
It was like
It wasn't a bad huge the people you hang with
Yeah, and that's not good people. They did fucking full of full of it
There's no sense in it because that's not the way you were going when you started out
I know. I mean, it's like and then but I've met really great people too and it's like there are some really great people like Alex. Oh, yeah.
And, uh, you know, like, you know, like you and, uh,
I'm just saying, I never would have, if you see me clinging to, it's going to fucking ass.
And I can see it coming from being an outsider.
I can see that this Alex man is going to fucking ass, you get me?
God that woman I was I was on her live
when I first met her it's a couple years ago and
We were hitting it off great
She was talking about coming out to Salem because it was like Halloween in a couple weeks and doing a collab with me
And I'm like fuck that sounds good, you know
And the next morning, I woke up and Tommy was on the panel and I jumped up there to talk to Tommy.
All of a sudden fucking Alex got bullshit. I was the biggest piece of shit.
Now had I known, I didn't know anything about fucking Tommy and fucking her screw in.
In all the background bullshit, so I'm in the dark about what's going on all of a sudden
I'm getting messages going straight. You don't know the background between these two and I'm like as I'm on panel
And I'm like holy shit, and then the next thing she found out that I was fucking bloggers
wife, you know and husband shit
and she went after him and went after his kid offline.
Then went after, I mean him,
her and Trishalicious went after fuckin' bloggers.
Kid, his ex-wife, and his parents offline.
So all of a sudden I took the weak strike on blogger
and I pinned those two bitches.
I showed exactly where they were on their phones.
And I fucking pinned him and I threw it up on my fucking
Community page on YouTube and YouTube gave me a weak strike
But I tell you what they left blog on fucking family alone after that
That's how I know their cunt and I know
Ow
Hey Joe, how you doing buddy? How you doing?
I'm doing good. I see you Tracy. I'm doing good. I know you sexy son, bitch
You sexy little sweet angel
Wow, that's how does that picture supposed to be psych. He never looked like that. What the hell's that supposed to be?
It's supposed to be some fucking angel or what are you a little angel psyche little fucking sword angel
are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding me are you kidding
kind of doesn't it's like a gym or
kind of looks like a sexy man
I suppose John King
now he's
ohhh
look at that little baby
dog to a kitty kitty
kitty get him
he's pool kitty
oh man it's 4.30 in the fucking morning
I just came up and say hi to you, Tracy.
I'm gonna dip out, but Tracy, you not only came up
and say hi to you, sweetheart.
Aw, you sexy bad.
I hope you're having a good Friday and a good weekend, baby.
All right?
Yeah, baby, let's get drunk.
All right, no, I'm gonna get drunk,
but I just gotta get out of here.
But I hope you know, you got my whole entire heart, Tracy.
That's my heart you got.
Baby, dude, baby, heart.
Ha ha ha ha.
Ooh, that's my heart.
Oh crazy bastard. He's such a sweetheart
He can rattle some cages, okay
That's why I love him
Okay, well, I'm looking for something funny
I can't find them. Well, I actually had a bunch of clips that I was like
My shorts
My shorts, but
My short video shorts
I thought we didn't do this anymore
Sure, here we go
Nope, you want me watch some shorts go ahead throw some shorts. They're very funny
You only rent beer
I mean, I'm GTA. You like GTA. Yeah, what do you play like mainly? That's not what you made me play. Well, I have a VR set now. I do different stuff. And I, uh, but I have played all the, all the final fancies, all like, are you, are you grooming this guy?
You know, like, um, Red Dead Redemption, I've played Grand Theft Auto's, I've played a lot of video games, I've played over a thousand of them.
He's, he's, he's just 30!
It's like, I can play them in Resident Evil?
He's got the mind of a five year old.
Resident Evil, yeah, I played Resident Evil Village, and um, and uh, I played like another one that was really good with the cannibal family.
Like, part three or something.
Oh, I don't know.
Anyway, so.
And then they, you know, they tack me into the chat and stuff.
I'm unmodded, and I feel I'm not her again, but eventually I'm just a little lady to do it, but I don't care.
It's going on, I don't know.
I'm dealing with a nut.
Scorpio, Ambino is like,
Oh, he's making songs about you.
To the vibe and don't
And they can't say she's not bullying you.
What is bullying?
What I'm trying to tell you is best.
Oh my God.
And is that really good?
She thinks I like made fun of her.
Oh my God.
The one for the $50 is that trick.
Because like, you know, it's like,
oh my God, right?
Anyway, she is, she's just
Okay, no.
So, I was going to tell everybody, you know how I said about stream yard, Tracy there?
Tracy left.
No.
Sorry, that was bad.
I was going to say, so stream yard.
Like this whole time they've allowed you like when they record like 50 hours from me whatever
So I've had the last 50 hours or whatever and a lot of shows I've deleted and stuff and so but they only have 50 hours
And they just they just start deleting stuff out of it and keep the new stuff
But you can go to the page of that
And that and it will say like generate AI clips and it will go through and it will
Yeah
And it's like the editor kind of together too like really cool and you can set that on automatic
Wherever you tell me to do a live
You hit that button where it'll make the clip and it'll clip something out of your live
And then throw it up there even if you're playing music behind it. You just get a copyright on this short
That's all fuck it
Yeah, and so like yeah, well so far it's been okay
I think I there's a lot of stuff to get the age restriction as people and I know now
I know what age restricts not like it's like when people say
Decad and it clips you being a dickhead and then you get a fucking I got a couple of them 18 plus
But I already had it on fucking it's not for adults when I do a live stream
Yeah. Yeah. But they don't want to go in advance and click it to fucking 18 plus and if you're doing YouTube. And they aren't monetizable. That's an issue with them. Well, the thing is, is 18 plus, you'll get the credit for the views, but they're not going to fucking publicize it. It's going to, if the AI is going to take it, take it. Curse.
Yeah, it'll be up. Yeah. So yeah, it's hard but it's hard to do YouTube anyway
And that's what you're trying to do. Yeah, but it's not gonna affect your channel
So you have to leave those ones that are 18 plus
And just have them up there and let them catch whatever they will yeah
Yeah, you still get the credit for the traffic and you can still have them up for 18 plus
I'm gonna basically they have to say like, you know, I guess I'm over 18 and then then it's like yeah
They're not like you have to like kind of like
Look for them rather than like these come across or just go across now
I get a lot of copyright strikes. So what I do is I leave them bastards up except for the one
full cut across
Strikes or it'll view in some countries and it won't view in others just because of copyright, but the ones that are solid
Then I'll get rid of that shit because ain't nobody gonna see it because youtube won't play it because of this too many copyrights
Well, they're not strikes though. No, they're yeah, well they can lead to it. Yeah, I've lost one two three
Four channels over bullshit. I
Lost one over a mod
This mod had another channel because they got hate speech and they were a mod on my channel
Fucking YouTube took all three of my fucking channels
including my monetized one because he was a mod so whatever he got he was
there connected with you watch out who you mod because if they're doing
something on their end that you don't know about and they get hit for hate
speech you're gonna get it yeah that's you better watch out who you mod yeah
Yeah, I only mod one motherfucker and that's my messenger
Are you a mod? Yeah, make me a mod again. No
All right
You gotta make God a mod are you gonna pay? Oh, please all right
Okay
You know if I can tell you said oh, please
Or is Cato little god Cato is pre-god. Oh my god double-wish for now
Oh my gosh, are you HP Lovecraft bang up that's pre-god
He's alright. He's alright. He's God. It's kinda weird. It's weird. I like that. I love him.
Pre-God. Before God there was Cthulhu. Cthulhu? The dreaming. The endless dreaming.
What you're doing, really? You don't know about the dreaming?
No, I have no fucking clue. There was a God before God. I thought God was it
No, there's other universes Tracy this pre universes and all that shit the big bang before the big bang was a unit another universe
There's these old gods that are like horrific. They're like these horrific monsters. Where are you reading this?
Is it is it from ancient Greek? No, it was like an early 20th century, right? Yeah, early 20th early 1920s
1920s
Rendition of what was before God?
Well, that was like the kind of like kid a lore about these different monsters and like these old ones
Thanks, but get him monster kind of stuff, you know, it's like oh
Like crazy, Tracy basically whatever you want, whatever you want to believe it is gonna be the truth for you. Well, that's chaos magic, right?
and he's uh uh linguistic and uh he can read ancient greek
and uh he was very christian very very very christian i mean did everything you know went to
The shit that he reads in ancient Greek about Christ
It's like wicked
Like they found Jesus in a pack along with a naked boy at fucking
Four o'clock in the morning or their house would
Rag wrapped around his penis with the muse on the rag, which means he was talking with child. What?
It's an ancient Greek
It's written. I've seen it
I'm on a m m o n or
a m and
Oh, and I would say spelling he's got a fucking YouTube channel
And it the shit that he was told to
Translate into Hebrew and then from Hebrew into English
It made the shit that he was reading was so diabolical that it made made him turn against Christ
Well
Man you fucking doctor when it comes down to it
They're probably just stories, right?
And there's different cultural reasons and different stories.
No, this is actually got dates and fucking Medea.
Medea, that's Greek mythology.
Well, that's, it wasn't mythology. Medea actually existed.
She was like a queen of
Yeah, and then the islands of
Cree
Yeah, those were all fucking ancient islands
You know that those people act it was warriors of women that would
hide you a command and and if he was suitable
Have your mate and then kill him
Just to keep their fucking population up, you know and sacrifice the male babies type shit. So there was no inbreeding
Sturble well shit happens, but you know us women can be bitchy at times
What yeah, I know
Make a web. I said it happens, but women can be bitchy at times. Oh
Well, it's only been one time. I've been close to killing a man. Oh shit. I gotta
My eyes are bleeding. I gotta get out of here. I'll see you. Okay. God. Love you. God
Look at this thing. It's like this cool Tom Tracy
It's any other video
But you would get it the shit that you're in the music that you're using and shit like that
You would get into this guy. I
Think I have the I have one more video. Let me see. Yeah, okay. Let's see what you got. What'd you make?
This is my placement in the Sagittarius in a 12th house
So I don't know what you're saying, but Sagittarius. That's December ain't it?
It's uh, yeah, but that's where my it's like, but it's like uh, it's
It's the house of my on my chart. That's the 12th house. And so it's like it's not necessarily I have Venus and a Neptune in there
The 12th house of Sagittarius. Mine's all mercury
But I can go over your chart too. I'm like fucking means but so here's uh, this is the pure
This is about my Venus and Sagittarius on the 12th house place
In the temple of silence where secrets are kept
Venus hides softly where dreams intersect
In the twelfth house of fire shadows ignite
Sagittarius aims through the dark toward the light
You love like a pilgrim on paths never known
Seeking the sacred where wild stars are sown
Your heart is a compass, it points past the veil
Total love that is boundless, a myth on the trail
Hidden arrows of love, they fly unseen
Through the caverns of spirit, through the infinite dream
Every secret devotion, every prayer to the skies
Venus in the twelfth
The Centaur rides quiet through jungles of night
Hunting for freedom, for truth dressed in light
That's one of the first ones done
Yeah
I didn't I didn't animate that one. It's like
They can you know, but I just like I just wanted to put
But I made the song and I wanted to play it tonight
And so I just like I can't animate those and stuff like that and I might you know
It's like I'm it just depends because I'm making you know, I'm doing all like
A lot of songs and things that because because these are early things you can listen to like about like your personal science and things
Like a lot of that was like did you make you up like a playlist?
Yeah, I'm yeah, I have them all like I have like a lot of songs though. I just bought another like
On your fucking page
Yeah, I'm going a bit of a permanent. I'm trying to get them to like if unspotify you can get them on spotify
But you can't just put them directly on there yet to put them on this other website and then you can like and I think I'll
I'll get I'll get the other oh my god. Oh my god. It's like crazy laws
It's your guess. Thank you for thinking you think you guys are you know, I think it's a cute song in like
I mean, but it's like it has meaning to me because it's like my placement
But if anyone wants me to like, you know, look up do songs for you in your placement
You can like contact me on this
My screen there's kind of a patient. It's like
Yeah, Joe loved that era
I don't know, I lost my ear.
Dude, I'm gonna go crash out.
Okay, bye sweetie.
No, hey, see you later, see you everybody.
Thank you, Tracy.
Tracy's crashing out, okay, well.
I hear another song, let's see.
I don't know, you guys might be bored,
but it's definitely one thing funny though.
mess where the trivia is rigged but we still say yes purple curtains swaying mods holding
And so it's like, um, it's always hands. However, that detail can change in five minutes. Right?
Right.
I'm like, because the future also is like really up to up to us to decide, right?
And so we're looking at generalizing these are the moment and things like that and some of the past
Murphy's law, come on
It's all on its mind
But I think people are led to certain people and I think like
Yeah, that's part of the chaos theory you still have free will on how to interact with all of them
Yeah, and if you decide a certain way it can go either good or bad for you
Right and we have just like we have free will like you know
Like we've we have free will from God to like do good or do evil or you can say from the higher divine starts
So we have this and there's also a free will versus determinism where it's like is it really all faded or is like they're really free
Well, but I think that we can
Like I think I think the angels
Ability to have free will yet. Yeah, the most people have to use it. No, right?
well
some people do and
Some people use it at that place, right
It's like we have a we can have a will towards evil or a will towards good
You know, it's like we can like you can choose to hurt people
We can choose to like be selfish and we can choose to like see that ourselves is separate from other people and like
Just work for ourselves
I think that is part of free will, but I think that's also part of against the divine
Right the God wanted us to like decide. Oh look who's coming up to say hello
Who I can't see
You will see
Oh, am I boring you I'm so sorry sir
I'm just yawning
You're just close. I know I was just kidding for recreation
What's up, psyche? How are you doing, buddy? Good. How are you doing today? How are you?
What about you, Mrs. Butterfly?
He said, how are you, Butterfly? Did you hear him? He's saying, how are you doing? Oh, I'm okay. I'm off today.
Two days, I don't work until Monday. I'm excited
We're going to hell every morning, huh? No more going to hell every morning. I
Don't work in the morning. I work in the afternoon
We're just going to hell at any time it's bad
Maybe we're maybe we're already in some kind of hell, you know, maybe like maybe the maybe we can create a heaven of hell a hell of hell of heaven, you know
I think we're kind of
Yeah, the duality, right? And we're kind of between the duality, right?
Tomorrow, but what is tomorrow?
222 very 222. Yeah, it's a good number nice angel number 25
22 22. Yep. Oh yeah. It is. 22. Yep. I'm uh, two is my curse number. Yeah. February
22nd 2000. Wow. It was my birthday. There's two two two two as well. Tomorrow is your birthday.
Thank you, you know, I've heard I've heard it said like that
One is like the most the most good number like the one is the best number because it's like unity
It's like the unity of everything and then two is like the duality and so it's like the most evil number
That's just like well, you know one way to think about it, but one way
Yeah, one way, and there's many ways to think it look at things, but
Also, that's two people together
Yeah, go ahead and talk to SIG for a second.
I'm just gonna be backstage while you talk to SIG.
You don't have to be.
Can I post some cards on you?
Yeah, go ahead.
What do you have a question for?
I don't have a question.
Okay.
Hold on a second.
No.
Okay
Sorry deciding what's deck to use I
Like this deck it's called exiles
Got beautiful artwork
So what's up, sig while I'm shy
Right and
It exists
Queen of pinnacles in reverse not have lawns in reverse page of swords four of swords and the four of cups
Oh and the judgment
Let me try a couple more.
This deck is messed up.
No wonder what a beautiful for you for this one.
Okay, five of swords.
Things he might not got up to use the bathroom
Little bit
How you like that picture
it kind of reminds me of this other picture of a deck I just got today that I'm looking at now
out of sight. Hi Tracy. I can't see the chat so
but I guess he missed it.
I'm listening. You're listening, but you're not saying the pictures. Pictures have a lot to say about it. I'll be there in a moment. Okay. I apologize. No problem. Pictures. I mean, well, drawings are depictions, usually these sorts of symbolic images.
Very old it's really funny you got the out-of-sight you got the out-of-sight card and he's kind of out of sight at the moment, right?
It's okay
Go on all right
Where is it I thought it was the other Tracy
I do that one. It's okay. It's very interesting. Five of swords.
And then this one came to mind out of sight. The fire in the background.
And then next I also do the two of sword. Two of cups.
I did get this new deck.
Shall we play with that?
Sure, yeah.
Oh, again.
Terror deck knight of wands and
Two of wands. No.
Two of cups jet knight.
What does that mean not of cups and two of wands
Hey, what does that mean which tarot deck it says the book proceed
Procedures the discovery of a mystery affecting the person for the better in a degree governed by the distance
And the two of ones, the road will forecast a long journey if near 44, a serious accident if near 29, a robbery.
And shocking.
I'm not sure what any of this means.
22.
Hey, hey, look, look, I'm a map dead.
Look, I'm sick sour.
I'm not sure what any of that means.
I'm a faggot.
What's wrong with being a caggot?
Well, no, there's nothing wrong with being being gay sick. You should know better than most
So show your man nipples show your big old nipples
See yours first
Okay, I'm grossed out
That guy likes to mess around he's all right
I'm not really he's not really all right, but he likes to mess around. No, I don't mind
So again, I'm not the biggest fan of him either
understand
What did I already say I
Think you read red
two to two portal
the portal
What did I just pull I
Showed it
Okay, understand the backwards to
But did you did you really pull those cards or did you select them manually? I did not select them manually
I didn't actually pull them see you know what?
I
Should have not see if I had not said anything
If I had not said anything about tomorrow being a day and those numbers came up, then I would be, then I, then I would be interested.
Well, the thing is, just before you came on, I talked about the 2-2 to portal.
And then you came on as soon as your birthday.
Yeah, but well, it is also,
but it is also a strange number because of numerology.
It's a strange number, right?
I really don't care if you think I pulled them out personally or not.
I shuffle and they fall out.
That's what fell out.
Two, two, two.
They're also playing cards.
They are.
Everything will be used.
Yeah, you know, I actually got a deck of game cards
Game cards go on those can be used to
Game cards, what do you mean like?
Like poker cards
All kinds of cards any cards can be used
But but they have to have some meaning on them. Don't they?
Numbers have meaning
Symbols have meaning
Everything has
Okay
Yes, this one is interesting
Something told me to get it so I did
Prepare yourself to defeat the chew curse when it materializes work with your fellow explorers to assemble the items needed
To defeat the omens and curses
The explorer part
It's a game deck, but
It has different things on it
It looks cool, but what does it mean? Like, is it what you interpreted it as or like?
I'm not sure yet. I'm still kind of studying it a bit.
My thing is, I think what I'll learn is different ways of reading it
when I actually start playing with it, the cooperation phase.
Yeah, I know it's backwards. I'm sorry. No, no, it's not backwards. Go back
You put that back backwards for you cooperation. No, it's not
these
Do one of the following we hold and show it
Now you can't really see you
Kind of like like the actual text of the card
It's like kind of it's just hard to see the whole thing
But this is a card game, right? Yeah, it's called the betrayal
Well, that's it. It's a game though
If I can clarify
Like, say, with divination, you know, you can, like,
you can, like, pour shells on a table.
You can use trivial pursuit cards.
Like, there'll be some kind of meaning there,
and there'll be, and so there's numbers,
there's locations, there's people,
and all these can have some kind of meaning,
and so you can do a divination from anything.
And so that's what basically I think she was trying to say, but I like I like how this is going guys
I'm just gonna let you guys continue
What cigarettes do you smoke?
No, I'm live, but this is a Vira
This is February 22nd
What is that the red red and blue?
Marlboro
Yeah, what is the red and blue mean?
Red and black or red and black. What does that mean?
See
Look, how's that different from a regular red pack? I'm not sure I
Just use it either that or I choose the red and gold or black and gold
I don't know
God, this is difficult
Different days I choose red and gold
Different days I choose red and black
And I see you have red on
and black hair
plus black on your shirt
What's in the back I behind you I see red green silver and black
Hmm right so what does this mean? And you wearing a green hat, right?
Hmm what does that mean
Not sure
What does it mean to you
They're just colors not everything is just
You talk about chakra usually is
You talk about chakras red is actually the
What is it psyche this sacral chakra?
Root chakra. Green is the heart chakra. Yep, root.
Black is the combining of both.
Black is actually a...
absence of every color, really, isn't it? Or is it white?
I don't remember.
I think white is an absence of all color.
There's a difference in...
Black is all of the colors combined.
energy colors and coloring when using painting and that kind of stuff as the
opposite. Wow, I think I've ever done any painting I'm really bad at art, anything art
So say you don't you know, so that's like you're you're saying you're lack creativity because like there's a lot of art
You're saying you're just more logical. You're like more
You look at the ones wearing the same colors colors shirt, are you have a green green on tiger butterfly? He's wearing the same color hat
I know
Yeah
right I
Just realized that
true
I would show what it says on my shirt, but it give away my location.
Dark time.
Oh god, I don't do that.
No.
What happened?
It's actually the local high school is...
what my shirt is your alma mater no my kids yes and no I'm not going to close
that location no you know I know why am I smiling like an idiot but it is cute
that we're matching
I think I've been wearing this hoodie for like a while now
The hoodie, I do have a orange hoodie. I go to hoodie. That's one
Actually bought last week
Yeah
Along with a pair of matching pajama pets. They're so freaking comfortable. Oh my gosh
That one Emily were pajamas
I think that like you know like
The with the chakra colors right and he has the green over his over his head and stuff like that's like the heart chakra is like
Yeah
Yeah, you have it around your heart
No
Chakra
There are the reaps chakra the sacred chakras is like yellow. Yeah
Solar plexus is the orange like the Sun, you know
then the heart is green and then the throat is blue and then the crown is
purple and the third eye is like an indigo kind of color right. Interesting to think
about. What am I wearing? I'm wearing kind of a black and white. Like a kind of black
thread pattern with a black collar.
Kind of hard to tell with the flashing lights.
I know. Well, I'll turn them off.
I mean, it's fine.
Just like a brave in the back room.
I have like a little party going on.
Sorry, I have to put my hair back up.
It was starting to fall out.
Is it but you know, you know, see it's sick is a little bit of a skeptic when it comes to this kind of stuff
But he's also open-minded enough to like yeah, he's also open-minded enough to like say say reach read my cards and things like that and
To listen and I like how he's listening and did you like how I did the 222?
Yeah
Yeah, so the 222
And she
the reason you
But yeah, also like she's like, you know, she's not like going and picking like looking for 222 and like picking them out
She's like just she was like shuffling those cards fell out like it's like and so it's it is like
It's not any matter to me
Because she knew that information about you
She's able to put it together quickly, you know, it would have meant maybe like you would have recognized that
but it's like because she knew like she recognized it, but she's not like
trying to like
You can orchestrate it, right? It's like and so and also when you brought up to 222
It was because she had brought up 222 before we were talking about the 222 and you're like my birthday is 222 like like
So she brought it up. So
It's like she was saying
Okay, it's interesting, it's interesting what I'm saying, it's kind of called synchronicities,
like do they...
Okay, now...
I'll shut up.
I'm going to do another thing.
What is that?
The chariot
I split the deck it was a reverse
You're not moving very fast
Or you're moving doubly fast a chariot
or something's coming towards you?
Something's coming towards me.
Interesting.
Ooh, King of Wands.
King of Wands.
And as you notice, what I'm doing is just splitting.
Justice.
I'm not shuffling, I'm not doing anything except the lover's reverse.
So what you're just reading out the what the cards titles are?
At this point, yes
Okay, so what are the what are all the cards saying?
Like can you read all of them so far what have they said?
Can you help me
What I mean, what do you think? What do you think? Well, you're reading the cards, right? What did you see I pulled?
What are they how do you interpret your psychic? I don't know I forgot me too
All right. Well, so then you don't you don't have the I mean did you put them back into the deck?
I didn't do anything with it, except
throw it all back together.
Correct, sir.
All right.
Okay.
Can you have a slide?
Okay, it was a king of wands.
Yeah, it was a king of wands, and it was a justice,
and it was a love, okay, you hear me?
Love is in reverse.
It was in reverse, right?
And so,
Okay, so one
Right
Because he doesn't he doesn't know tarot at all and he's I don't know
You're just me for your for your gut feeling about it, right lovers reverse that means like a breakup that means like
some kind of like
Okay
The lovers themselves can actually consider the duality to two two of the inner workings
of yourself.
So you're trying to maybe work on your own inner divine masculine feminine balancing
yourself to two two.
Sick were you were you involved in a breakup that was like it was like meant to be kind of and it was like
karmic reasons for it and
You're also like the king of ones. Yeah, it's like I think that's you like a very passionate fiery person
No, no
But I don't want to backseat read. I don't want back. I mean all these things have happened to like everyone
Know but this is significant. This is just a significant significance for you right now
In your energy right now, not just like right. Okay, so go ahead. I'll let you guys I don't want to backseat read. I'm sorry
No, by all means
Backseat read. I have no problem
Okay, I'll be back. It's your channel back. I want you guys to talk. I want you guys
I think I think you guys are doing I don't I would think you guys are doing well like I think you know
it's like
Kind of like pulling teeth a little bit with him, you know, it's like and he's like gonna be a little bit
Tell me exactly what he's very he said he said he's not doesn't have the artistic side, right?
He's saying he's saying he's very left left or he's very right brand
I think he has a lot more artistic side than he thinks he does. I agree. I agree. I think he I think he does
But he that's what he says. I don't I'm bad at art. I don't know that color. I don't have an ass
The thing is that you're you are reading the cards
And so it's like, you're supposed to tell me what they mean,
but you're like asking me what they mean.
That's what it is.
I didn't say that.
I asked you what cards I pulled.
Because you didn't ask her a question.
Because I didn't remember.
Yeah, you didn't ask her a question.
You said, just pull the cards.
I just told you the cards I pulled.
Yeah, and so she's asking you, what does this mean to you?
And I took them back from the deck.
Yeah.
And so
Come on
When you see the picture on the card
Picture, yeah, you'll you'll have a feeling about it. You'll have a your own interpretation and it's like and then she wants to
The answer with the banter with you about that right and she
Yeah, it's nice because it's like when it's like so one's like
being so kind of, you're kind of being cold, right?
You're being very-
You're getting irritated as heck.
Yeah, it's okay.
Someone said, a BG said, this is the only panel
he's even allowed on, he's banned everywhere else.
Yeah.
So.
I find my way.
You find your way, huh?
Granted.
You know what?
Never mind
You'll hate it there
But he's there's more that he's he's getting he's getting I can see he's getting the he knows what you're talking about
He's getting the feeling
He's like I'm not gonna give her anything. I'm not gonna give her anything because she'll that's just giving her information
Then she'll just like
You know, I don't have any questions. I mean, you continue telling me what you think it
Hey, what's up, psyche? How you doing? How are you? I'm doing all right
What are you up to? I was just chillin. I was on it. I
Had a fun night
Alice's
No, I was I was just talking to Jim Nick, but she you're talking to Jim
I don't know if I should say this, but she left me backstage for like an hour
She left you backstage what like a freak off
well
No, not me and her but I like she didn't I think she like forgot to exit out her phone
But she she then she started talking to someone and I'm not gonna get into it. Okay, but did you have a romantic night?
As like a third wheel, maybe who is this tour that who is the first two wheels?
What do you mean it came well
Who's your next boyfriend's guys blackout Andy I
Don't know who it is who would it be anyone know
It wasn't black out
With a beta
that'd be hot yeah well I mean if it's like two girls it was two girls it was
too rough how many guys oh my god how many guys were there you're getting I'm
not gonna kiss and tell you but how many guys were there just you you're the
only guy was it all women there is someone else there's another guy did you
like she didn't know like she shut the stream down
but I was like
like I didn't really I thought it was over
even because I had my thing muted and then like I could like
still hear him talking and I'm like wait and he's like alright shut off the
stream she's like I shut down the stream
and then they just like talk they you know
I was being a little voyeuristic, I guess.
You were?
Did you have out your...
No, not at all.
I was just like...
You take out the monster.
Can I show the picture of you?
No.
I'm not drunk right now.
Wait until I'm drunk and stuff.
I'm not going to get drunk tonight.
After you leave, can I do it?
No, just like like I don't want you showing that unless I'm like here for real
I remember when I showed it like several times that night
Like I don't know. I'm not really in that mood right now. Okay. I'm sorry. Sorry. So Jimmy
Oh, dude, would you have a threesome with base episode base surfer and Jimmy?
No
I was just listening
Okay, you're just listening I'm playing guitar
It's I don't know. I like I was like, I don't know I didn't want to say anything like
We'll say it we've already said enough. I mean you said Jim Nick and the several guys
it was just funny
it's funny
I think Jim Nick's a nice girl
you know that Chris K said I can give him oral sex
on chatterbait and he'll do chatterbait with me
and he's gonna come up with $100,000 for me
that sounds like something he would do I guess
yeah
You're done in Tim
No
No, are you sure?
Yeah, I've never like I've never I've never even kissed a guy before
I'll be your first
Dude, I had like this chance to like if I would have kissed my best friend
I think I've told this story before like
This girl literally said like I'll let you guys do whatever you want to me if you guys make out and we wouldn't do
And where you just left the room and you're like, oh, never mind like like kind of like I mean I hit third base
So she let me do that. She's up. She's like, oh, you didn't make out with them. No more
No home run you're gonna get I
Dude, I slept with that girl's sister too. I had a gruesome with her sister. Oh my god with that the catcher of the team
She was like
Well, their mom is a lesbian actually. Oh my god
We actually have a nice pleasant night. I don't know I think it's not that bad like their parents got divorced because their mom was a lesbian
Well, I think that I've had having better vibrations better luck with me
I had a good uh, good uh, gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig gig
I started I was streaming a little bit last last year just on the lives for a walk until I got the open panel in January
Since then everything just took off all of a sudden they had like
But well, I did have like a decent chat
They had probably like between five and ten people in my chat
But I started out for the first and that's that's because I had made a lot of contact with something even that's pretty good
For like, you know, a lot of people don't get people in their chat
And so I said, yeah, do you have to network a little bit and it's like, you know
You're an attractive, attractive girl. It would probably help, you know, obviously, but, uh, you know, me
I just had to, like, you know, be creative and use cool thumbnails and kind of, like, give you content
to make your people and, like, went to different shows and stuff. I can give you good advice if you want to start streaming.
I'm almost done with streaming. I actually, like, I'm in a new channel. I'm gonna start from scratch.
Well, good!
I mean that's probably a good thing. I think there's probably ways to reset your algorithm too. I'm not sure but it's like, I think, uh...
I just imagine it's crazy. Like, there's so much random shit on there. Like, it's just not even like, I don't know, like, telling people.
Well, that's like, that's one of the styles. Like, there's people doing really well that just don't have, they don't stick to their genre. They just go to like, to fit us to different stuff.
And it's like, kind of popular.
Yeah, I don't really want to do that though. Like, I don't really like the whole, like...
I don't know, I don't really like the friend simulator part of it, like...
Well, just do what you want, you know, but then make real friends. I mean, it's like,
you're gonna be hanging out long enough to, like, actually get to know people, bond with them and,
like, you know...
Actually make a friend. That's what I'll tell people like I just have like way too many mods and stuff
And it's like I'll see like if you want to be in my mod like DM me
Yeah, I mean like a nude photo. Do we like me to send you a new photo?
You want to take your picture my cat
I
Yeah, I'm so yeah, so I don't know we're like we're just looking at some different stuff today like
Do I see if I'm funny? Let me see. I'm sure it's great. My friend just had like a super rare cat like
Her like a bleak. Her cat gave birth to one. It's a what is it? It's a
It's like only like point
Zero three percent of cats or this type of cat
So it's a male
Tortoise shell point zero four percent for males
So only one in three thousand tortoise shells are male
I'll just play my flute
So they actually climb felt like
Are you still there pipes? Yeah, can you hear me? Are you gonna picture a camera ever?
Pipes I don't know
Hey, can you hear me pipes check what it mirrors at him
what's going on okay well I stayed way too long anyway and so thank you guys for
being here and I'll play this song on the way out to the audio I'll play this
great video. Is it not working? Yo, check. Good night guys.
Okay, guys, I'll play the song on the way out. Good night guys. It's been a great day
I have to go a bit anyway, and like it can't be based
Yeah
But I'm glad you stayed with me. Thank you so much everybody. It was great. I'll play you a song on the way out
But I hope you have a wonderful night
Sleep well, don't have to pay for it. Bye
I'm pleasant to you. Elvira was the opposite. I should play this one. I'll do this one
Right
where the echoes fall with tarot in hand hearing every call from praise to venom